kod1cs: hi n
ekalsuwaidi: hello :)
twitchcansuckmydeek: Do you know about psychology
kod1cs: teach me C language
aymanpoquito: yo
kod1cs: i pay you 10cents for week
jax05_: what's up everyone
leopp: yo
logi6000: what up diggity dog
small_beautiful_asian: hey
oMythra: georgy boi
twitchcansuckmydeek: I went on a girl's stream and I wanted to ask something random. Something related to science. And I asked
adibaby04: weord george
unluckychickenn: PogChamp
twitchcansuckmydeek: Do you know what a rectifier is
tiagodopke: good evening broo
zol0: holy shit he's live PogChamp
logi6000: George the man
twitchcansuckmydeek: do you think my unconscious did that
logi6000: the myth
aymanpoquito: were back boiz
alreye: nice ass btw
adibaby04: good evening
ImJ4Gu4R: Dem boiyzz, Im not finish yet watching yesterday video lol
logi6000: the legend
twitchcansuckmydeek: read the whole story dude
zoprano21: @georgehotz do you run kali linux?
logi6000: what up diggity dog
alxhotel: what is carla ?
santtiagoo: We back boooyyzzzzzz 🙉
MrMcaustin1: Hows it going george
twitchcansuckmydeek: I hate python
logi6000: Carla is a self driving car sim
santtiagoo: My exs name used to be carlas
alxhotel: ah nice
adibaby04: yo man would you review my github
twitchcansuckmydeek: anus
aymanpoquito: @twitchcansuckmydeek why
logi6000: what's the ban topic today
MrMcaustin1: Same as normal logi6000
twitchcansuckmydeek: because I don't like snakes and pythons became too widespread
zoprano21: I CANT C
twitchcansuckmydeek: I like C
logi6000: cool
logi6000: wait so no comma ai on a openpilot stream
mrmusicmaine: Sweeeeet I was allowed into the stream (: sometimes I can’t bc I’m not a subscriber. I will subscribe once I get some steady income
hofergabriel: nietzche!
LaheyFPS: LaheyFPS subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
logi6000: I don't got a job so I can't sub.
Orionmyth: slm aşkım <3
GamerulSadic: Did you really put this guy to subscribe and that face tho 🤣🤣
prakyath_kantharaju: Fuck me you made it!!!
MrMcaustin1: Thanks LaheyFPS for the sub!
twitchcansuckmydeek: I saw you on youtube doing pentest thought you were about infosec but I guess it's more of self driving cars and stuff
THATTACHYON: THATTACHYON subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
crispyvideo: Is this mapping data from google maps api?
MrMcaustin1: thanks THATTACHYON
FresherLemons: man it's a good night for chewing ice
logi6000: @twitchcansuckmydeek you must be new around here
twitchcansuckmydeek: yes i am
ne3cross: @georgehotz do you use Tensorflow?
foogs_: im chewing ice right now. it feels good. helps me concentrate.
hofergabriel: what's your project euler friend key?
zol0: wait if everyone shits on python for being slow why is it used for self d/riving car software, for the ML libraries
zol0: ?
adibaby04: im
adibaby04: adibaby04 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
erichtp: @bocewnoce dont say that D:
logi6000: he is cool he makes self driving cars with commai. was first to jailbreak iPhone. and got sued by Sony. @twitchcansuckmydeek
crispyvideo: Keyboard? It’s some sort of a mechanical lol
twitchcansuckmydeek: oh lol
logi6000: he uses hhkb pro 2
eaglesemanation: there is some pasta sauce on your keyboard
adibaby04: im subbed now
LaheyFPS: LUL
gusfrehse: ruby is much better
earthbender: LUL
adibaby04: https://github.com/adiprerepa
crispyvideo: Annoying loud sound haha
fusight: Thanks @adibaby04
MrMcaustin1: crispyvideo watch out
oMythra: they're back with the K word smh
crispyvideo: I can’t take loud clicks and crap. Very annoying
logi6000: cinnamon rolls are the best dinner
brbdontdie: haha he is going to eat a coffee maker and cina rolls
mumubecks: gusfrehse I like ruby too
Noomers: its 3 am here
thundershots999: breakfast for dinner is anarchy!
logi6000: is there any tea this stream? @georgehotz
crispyvideo: You take the map data from google api? I noticed Tesla does not
erichtp: did you ever finish the mac compatibility >
mutrx: rate our github profiles
prakyath_kantharaju: https://carla.readthedocs.io/en/stable/carla_server/ check this out for communication it is very interesting!!
twitchcansuckmydeek: self driving cars sound really boring tbh
logi6000: don't rate mine it's a mess
adibaby04: @georgehotz can i haf review
adibaby04: wait yeah rate contest
brbdontdie: lol if you think self driving cars are boring then what do you find interesting @twitchcansuckmydeek
GamerulSadic: im really courius how long ( and if ) comma ai could overtake other self driving cars .
prakyath_kantharaju: @twitchcansuckmydeek are you serious!!! Self driving cars are cool AF.
MrMcaustin1: George already said no GitHub reviews kiddos
crispyvideo: Once you go self drive. And electric. You can’t go back
xx_owlcapwn_xx: @twitchcansuckmydeek what is the point of self driving cars LUL
logi6000: Is George verified yet on Instagram
crispyvideo: I did 320 miles today and don’t even feel jt
santtiagoo: nop not verified yet
logi6000: that's fucked
ajtourville: Is CARLA like Tesla DOJO?
brbdontdie: were you asleep @crispyvideo
prakyath_kantharaju: Why not ros?
crispyvideo: Nah why would I be asleep lol
foogs_: lmaO
twitchcansuckmydeek: What do I find interestin? I will tell you what. I saw a dutch chick yesterday. Doing an art installation. She directed twitch messages into an arduino which drove the electrodes she sticked on her various parts. Hacking that in real time would be interesting.
abk467: saved
krouzux: krouzux subscribed at Tier 1.
thundershots999: i'm up to 3 bags a day
foogs_: im chewing ice right now
logi6000: @thundershots999 hahaha
MrMcaustin1: inb4 ice chewing becomes a banned topics
abk467: abk467 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 4 months!
FresherLemons: Sonic ice is the best for chewing
FresherLemons: FresherLemons subscribed with Twitch Prime.
brbdontdie: define various parts
xxxdeja: No chewing ice gang
ajtourville: Thanks for the HahaHide @krouzux
Doyniish: Doyniish subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! you are so mint
prakyath_kantharaju: is open pilot communication similar to ros master,node communication ?
MrMcaustin1: The amount of subs today is crazy
adibaby04: Thanks for the HahaSleep @doyniish
champ900: @georgehotz what's your goal in life
twitchcansuckmydeek: arms mainly
logi6000: George can you recommend me any shows. Mr robot is about to end so I need a new show
mrmusicmaine: so I’m not sure what the title is implying. When you say “Open pilot for everyone” are you talking about car compatibility?
foogs_: geo hotz yes! is what they're actually chanting
thundershots999: no maroon 5 tonight?
Tsoding: tsodinKomrade gde nas net
MrMcaustin1: Partner open pilot with nueralink so the computer can drive our bodies
thundershots999: lmao
mrmusicmaine: @champ900 he wants to live in the future. Get rid of jobs bb. AGI.
ne3cross: How simple/difficult is it to add unsupported models?
adibaby04: this shit trash tho
robby0313: Thanks for the HahaDoge @doyniish
CianKy: Super random, but is anyone here particularly proficient with Prolog?
twitchcansuckmydeek: I have never thought I could get that excited about hacking until I saw a hot dutch chick with electrodes on her body connected to the twitch chat through a lousy arduino
twitchcansuckmydeek: live
krouzux: uh
xxxdeja: D:
xx_owlcapwn_xx: wtf @twitchcansuckmydeek
twitchcansuckmydeek: and she was in an art gallery exhibiting
oMythra: Prolog sucks part of my final tomorrow has it lol
CaptCalifornia: wtf is this psycho listening to
twitchcansuckmydeek: If only I had the skills...
Knarez: what is your tmux or screen philosophy here
brbdontdie: It sounds like you are interested in art then
ne3cross: @georgehotz multithreaded of multiprocessing?
thundershots999: Have you tried open pilot in the snow?
adibaby04: USE gRPC NOT THIS INTERNAL CRAP
ne3cross: Or*
robby0313: What are some good books I should buy?
Tsoding: @georgehotz, the one with a better quality https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CFKhLYqUA0Q
CianKy: @oMythra it absolutely does, I have an assignment due in the morning which I have totally neglected haha
lua_320: @brbdontdie ones that you can read
adibaby04: kafka
Tsoding: kafka LUL
twitchcansuckmydeek: I like java
Jeppelelle: redit
gseven_: nats
adibaby04: still grpc
xx_owlcapwn_xx: java WutFace
THATTACHYON: Its written in scala I think
logi6000: Java can go suck a deek
adibaby04: you can
twitchcansuckmydeek: I don't like not having direct access to the memory but I like java
gseven_: nats.io @georgehotz
THATTACHYON: Rabbit MQ ?
adibaby04: nsq?
logi6000: python master race
CaptCalifornia: LMAO
ne3cross: Qt
gseven_: its really good and simple
adibaby04: when have you used gRPC?
Singha360: yo yo
tsAllySparkles: got a comma dev kit for christmas ;)
gseven_: yeah a client @georgehotz
ne3cross: Rabbit?
Singha360: @georgehotz what's your opinion on Flutter and Dart as a programming language?
gseven_: there is a nats.py @georgehotz
CianKy: @georgehotz have you used Prolog before?
Jeppelelle: Implement pub sub on your key/val db you built in another stream?
adibaby04: nsq?
logi6000: George did you get inspired by sentdex
logi6000: for carls
logi6000: carla
tkrsh009: hows it going bros
yeah_haey: So you arent playing ctfs anymore ☹️
gseven_: really high @georgehotz
fishsource: hey everyone what's the project for today?
adibaby04: https://nsq.io/ exists
Doyniish: lmao
1monkjuice: "EON DevKit Make driving chill"
gseven_: better docs though
CaptCalifornia: Nats is General Availability as a service
CaliburOne: hey ladies... im generally available KappaHD
THATTACHYON: RabbitMQ !!
fishsource: what looking for? video streaming library?
mrmusicmaine: Lmfaooo fuuuuq NATS
adibaby04: its all tcp lol
mumubecks: Why there are so many messaging libraries. Where are they used?
logi6000: so what exactly does cereal do
adibaby04: why not gRPC tho whats its problem?
krouzux: gRPC is a nightmare to use
0Day_H4X0rz: Guten Morgen/Good Morning von/from Deutschland/German prelyerLove pimpli2PimpEY prelyerKiss HahaCat
death_gadget: Somebody drank the gRPC kool-aid
adibaby04: thats fair
adibaby04: ima write some documentation then
krouzux: you know I think Twitch even made their own RPC thing using protobuf because they got annoyed with gRPC lmao
logi6000: so what do the messages do in these programs. what is the point
adibaby04: messages are whats sent my dude
adibaby04: from a struct to over-the-wire
logi6000: I know what's the point
logi6000: what's the use
adibaby04: what else would you do?
adibaby04: its the best way to send/recv info
gseven_: who doesn't use docker lol
gordopeIotudo: what terminal interface do you use on windows?
logi6000: send over different computers
adibaby04: @logi6000 can you explain what ur saying
adibaby04: i mean wanna use pure rest and some spring boot shit?
Crowz4K: @georgehotz hi
logi6000: so what is the whole point of something like cerial
mumubecks: I dont get it neither. Whats the use
adibaby04: its lightweight sending and recieving pub sub bro
Crowz4K: @georgehotz how log will you stream?
adibaby04: its super useful
adibaby04: pub sub at least
adibaby04: @georgehotz you answer
logi6000: define pub sub
adibaby04: the q
1monkjuice: publisher subscriber
adibaby04: its basically publishing messages to a topic
logi6000: ohhhh thanks I get it now
Knarez: did this guy learn to type yesterday
Knarez: Kappa
adibaby04: which there are other computers subscribes to that topic
Th3G4mingbros: Th3G4mingbros subscribed with Twitch Prime.
adibaby04: so they get that message
cogforkd: OMG ... Hi George
logi6000: I get it. I FINALLY UNDERSTAND SOMETHING!!!!!
adibaby04: ive never heard of cereal but im gna try it out i guess
adibaby04: @georgehotz whats the performance like?
thundershots999: Where are the cinnamon rolls?
logi6000: yeah where the rolls at
tsAllySparkles: why do you use vim?
logi6000: vim is superior
adibaby04: how though??
gseven_: does it guarantee delivery ?
adibaby04: no shit
adibaby04: thats what tcp is
Joogurt: i don't get what most of the stuff you do, but i still love watching you
logi6000: once you get used to key shortcuts it is far better and more efficient
gseven_: does it guarantee delivery ? @georgehotz
brbdontdie: yeah, i found that although vim has a lot of cool features, i actually still work faster with other text editors.
brbdontdie: maybe I am not using enough shortcuts
logi6000: you just need to get used to HJKL and a lot gets easier from there
1monkjuice: brbdontdie, can you use those other text editors when working on a server?
logi6000: unless he uses nano
adibaby04: for performance why dont you use nanopb? https://github.com/nanopb/nanopb
logi6000: @georgehotz look at post above me
brbdontdie: ah no. all my programming experience has been for school projects. I haven't actually worked on any industry projects yet.
mumubecks: Do self driving cars have crontab?
adibaby04: @brbdontdie its hella easy to get into industry if ur in school btw. im 15 and have had an internship at a tech company and its lit.
leander_ms: George be my daddy
logi6000: @adibaby04 you can get an internship at 15? I'm 13 so I don't knwo
c19946: use vscode for markdown
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz https://github.github.com/gfm/
brbdontdie: Haha, I got my first real internship at 21
adibaby04: @logi6000 it was at life360, they were small enough to take me but still pretty big
brbdontdie: kudos to you dude
logi6000: oh.
adibaby04: just do side projects
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz just add python after the first ''' to get syntax highlighting for MD
logi6000: that's still amazing what country
brbdontdie: I am about to begin work full time for a pretty large tech company
adibaby04: the coding interview is actually easy
adibaby04: united states
brbdontdie: fairly soon
logi6000: ok
krouzux: i think working on personal projects is better way to start off than working in the industry
adibaby04: damn @brbdontdie nice
krouzux: the industry is a scam
knilecrack: wsup
adibaby04: yea fs but to get into industry you need personal projects
brbdontdie: nothing based in silicon valley though
c19946: wrap your code in ```python CODE ```
logi6000: life360 is what my parents used to use
knilecrack: still trying to get openai to work for mac?
adibaby04: yea its in SF
logi6000: yea where I'm at there not many tech companies
adibaby04: where are you at?
logi6000: is but in a spot where there aren't many
logi6000: not is us
adibaby04: state?
logi6000: east coast. I'll give you that
adibaby04: o damn gotchu
logi6000: I'm guessing you in SF
adibaby04: bay area
logi6000: oh
adibaby04: i went to SF every day tho over the summer
thundershots999: anyone else getting buffering?
tsAllySparkles: fix the strings on your hoodie plz
krouzux: lmao
logi6000: nice. I wish I could go
brbdontdie: I've always wanted to go. A buddy of mine is going to stanford for his phd. I'm so envious.
adibaby04: shit thats cool
logi6000: there isn't shit in the east coast and especially not shit that will intern at 15
adibaby04: just make a github and do projects
adibaby04: literally my boss just looked at my projects and interviewed me
abstracticism: what is carla?
logi6000: yeah I do that but most of the time I just can't come up with ideas
brbdontdie: yeah. Having projects is huge.
mickjaggerrrr: DUDE ur a fkn legend george
logi6000: your boss found you
brbdontdie: try implementing things that other people have already made.
logi6000: or u contacted
adibaby04: i contacted first
logi6000: ok
adibaby04: but then i went and interviewed
brbdontdie: It isn't important that you come up with something new. Just make something, understand how it works, and try to learn from it
adibaby04: yeah because with that you can make new stuff
logi6000: I guess I have 2 years to try and work toward a internship. any advise
adibaby04: start programming lol
braininavatt: LUL
1monkjuice: sit your ass down and code
adibaby04: make a github
logi6000: hmm
adibaby04: @1monkjuice amen
logi6000: ha
evoxrocks: OMG thank you so much for the 10,000 bits!!
logi6000: what language does life 360 use
MrMcaustin1: YOUR PHONE GEORGE IT DO THE VIBRATE
adibaby04: so for android its java and kotlin, ios swift
knilecrack: damn homie
adibaby04: and backend is in PHP, Java, and Go
brbdontdie: I wouldn't go as far as to say that university is a scam, but anything you learn in a lecture could be self-taught by getting your hands dirty and doing some good ol googliing
KNOOKEL_HEAD: Kreygasm
logi6000: nice what do you code in
nso1995: yummy tidfe pods
krouzux: groceries delivered
Th3G4mingbros: objective-c for iOS for life
abk467: tide pods .. we eating good tonight
bebos16: PogChamp
adibaby04: I code in Java and Go, with some C Mainly
xxxdeja: A man of culture
logi6000: cool I am pretty fluent in python and working on go
adibaby04: go is great
braininavatt: HahaDoge
nso1995: A Pagan channel
12btw_: BlessRNG
Doyniish: Merry Christmas
KNOOKEL_HEAD: merry christmas ANELE
THX1342: wrap yourself in it
Rlchibi: I kinda wwant to learn go
adibaby04: just learn it lol
adibaby04: its not hard
THX1342: now you just need to dye your hair pink and do ASMR streams
logi6000: yeah. I really want to learn c but after learning python everything in other languages seem like a chroe
Knarez: monkaS
c19946: most beautiful thing i ever seen
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @logi6000 same
logi6000: yup
THX1342: @logi6000 learn assembly, then you'll learn to appreciate C
jax05_: wait until he cracks the bulbs by sitting on them
nso1995: Consumerism makes all things better
abk467: it's beginning to look alot like Christmas
logi6000: ok
mumubecks: BlessRNG allahu christmas
thundershots999: i got off of tide pods and went to ice
brbdontdie: @THX1342 Learn verilog, then you will appreciate assembly
THX1342: LUL
logi6000: the weather outside is weather. who knows where that from?
brbdontdie: haha jk. nothing is worse than assembly
Rlchibi: its never too late for coffee
thundershots999: coffee black with 15 sugars
KNOOKEL_HEAD: POGGERS
THX1342: I like assembly tbh
CianKy: @georgehotz have you used prolog before?
brbdontdie: I understand that it has value, but I don't like having to write several lines to do something that would take me 1 line in C
THX1342: I just study it to pwn
nso1995: This keyboard is horrible
logi6000: the languages I would like to know are python, go, bash, and c
THX1342: not sure if there is any other use in modern times... compilers are hard to beat
nso1995: It sounds like you're typing on a slab of metal
Jeppelelle: How does it bypass the kernel?
logi6000: I got about half
logi6000: topre switches the best
thundershots999: @nso1995 we dont talk about the hardware typing device
logi6000: LMFAO
mumubecks: Why not upload with ftp from windows explorer
krouzux: lmao
zeroeagle1: what we doing today
logi6000: fucking ftp
brbdontdie: I had to utilize some inline assembly for a project I was doing in OS
thezilion: and licence?
knilecrack: put them on your head
logi6000: it's good Christmas chair
THX1342: christmas lights on the chair are proper ASMR streamer decoration
zol0: in dish washer
krouzux: put the lights out of view where the deserve to be
tsAllySparkles: nice bootay
moonify: Now we know to not put F lights in ours chairs.
logi6000: @krouzux someone is not in the spirit
lemsa_: best decoration ever
visudo20179c: bogaLeak bogaLeak bogaLeak bogaLeak bogaLeak bogaLeak
thundershots999: !sr holly jolly christmas
mrmusicmaine: I love it when George gets philosophical
fatboyruuuun: What programming is this ? is this python or ruby ?
mutrx: merry christmas?
Rlchibi: python @fatboyruuuun
logi6000: who's that guy who put his cat in a box and said he didn't kill his cat because he didn't look at the cat when it was dead
mutrx: send it to one of ur viewers
nso1995: You can actually make coffee in a waffle maker
krouzux: cooking stream when?
braininavatt: giveaway! PogChamp
logi6000: @nso1995 that seems risky
mutrx: equivalent excahnge
mutrx: fucking weeb
krouzux: oh weeb shit
tiagodopke: weeb
krouzux: turn that off
brbdontdie: yoooooo. that was one of the best intros to an anime ever
Th3G4mingbros: I've been meaning to watch it but haven't yet
mutrx: u watch Made in Abyss
SheitanasGM: i luv FMA
logi6000: turn that furry or whatever shit off
tsAllySparkles: dude what are you on
knilecrack: oshi kuru
brbdontdie: i used to get so hype listening to this intro
fatboyruuuun: Edward <3
mutrx: wowow full autismo
tiagodopke: that makes no sense
abk467: SeemsGood
knilecrack: only for you
Th3G4mingbros: lmao
thundershots999: did you throw out the old macbook?
FresherLemons: george out here spitting facts
moonify: test it
AWZ123: what editor is that?
mutrx: what other anime do u watch
knilecrack: only when you are boujee
logi6000: no waffle maker is better than coffee maker. throw out coffee maker get tea maker
fatboyruuuun: just don’t lose a arm and a leg in the process
moonify: @AWZ123 vim
nso1995: But you already paid for it
AWZ123: @moonify thanks!!
tiagodopke: so are you saying that our lives can't improve in value?
nso1995: which was the loss
xxxdeja: A man of culture uwu
logi6000: @tiagodopke exactly
brbdontdie: next thing you know, george is going to try to bring back the coffee maker and it will come back as a full chainmail suit
tiagodopke: damn
krouzux: its like saying to gain your manly hood your virginity must be losted
fatboyruuuun: I got it, makes sense
mutrx: https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSjyCoefTXVQlqoikqYLiKs_tCBWAJt56EHeIz038DTcHqj7Brs
mutrx: https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU
CaliburOne: you lose a arm and a leg and a your buddies whole body and you get back a pile of gore called mom
logi6000: @krouzux it's not equal value.
thundershots999: play some burl ives
tsAllySparkles: are you on meth
mutrx: @georgehotz https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU @georgehotz https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU @georgehotz https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU
logi6000: no he's not on meth
mutrx: monkaHmm
tsAllySparkles: what is his deal then lmao
visudo20179c: he's on math
zetleri: never do math
mutrx: PO unboxing stream
logi6000: he's to smart he would be Walter instead cooking instead of using
braininavatt: ninja? PogChamp
brbdontdie: is this george's way of saying he is moving to mixer?
logi6000: @brbdontdie I fucking hope not
moonify: So Ninja nows makes coffe makers/
krouzux: @logi6000 purity for adulteration seems equivalent
1monkjuice: we need an ai coffee maker
tanoshiizo: Does it connect to the internet?
AWZ123: that's money, you get something of value and you give money for it
thundershots999: he does realize he has to run a few cycles to clean the coffee maker?
Jeppelelle: What if one does not think anything has any value? Can one keep everything?
zetleri: money is just saved energy
tsAllySparkles: @thundershots999 i don't think he cares
lemsa_: "ninja make me a cofee"
mutrx: drinking coffee at 630pm LUL
1monkjuice: @zetleri passive energy
brbdontdie: so what is the equivalent exchange for self driving cars :O
krouzux: if it doesn't connect to the internet it isn't cool
logi6000: @georgehotz you gave your money for the coffee maker you made your equal exchange
visudo20179c: gasoline powered cars
mutrx: does it have a bluetooth app?
logi6000: let's go
loktarcek: @visudo20179c *Diesel
logi6000: may the hunt for the maker begin
braininavatt: brb, travelling to San Diego
raulciuntastefan: if its nice why u arent keeping it ? Kappa
JonThomasK: yes
krouzux: george is indulged into weeb philosophies
visudo20179c: poopoo peepee
AWZ123: no? what?
brbdontdie: *gets a first class ticket to san diego to get george's waffle maker*
thundershots999: clean the coffe pot
mutrx: 2 shots of vodka
logi6000: the hunt has begun. george where do you live
THX1342: I bet somewhere in the world there's a weeb who photoshoped geo's face in their body pillow
blondephilia: isn't 2 scoops a 4chan meme?
knilecrack: wash them 1st please
mutrx: tea > coffee
thundershots999: this is going to turn into a George getting sick stream
presidentkanyewest2024: hi
thundershots999: Clean the coffee maker
brbdontdie: @THX1342 please don't use weeb in your joke as an insult. Us weebs find that offensive
THX1342: LUL
krouzux: too late
aa_ato: ads
itsChoudhry: I wanna travel to where george lives to run into him. Ask him for a picture and have a irl flame war then he like hey was cool meeting you and leave.
thundershots999: you are suppose to run a few pots of just water first
mortalog: SURE LUL
visudo20179c: is the word weeb have speech?
JonThomasK: do you have a robot vacuum
lemsa_: @thundershots999 true
raulciuntastefan: What's a weeb's favorite element ?
logi6000: when can we go back to smoking weed and coding for 10 hours straight
raulciuntastefan: Manga-nese
anup_kodlekere: whats coookin?
raulciuntastefan: kill me now
brbdontdie: boron @raulciuntastefan
1monkjuice: -george programming self driving cars -youtube recommendation algo: "Microsoft word tutorial, how to insert images"
Thealvisz: Can I have a picture AND waffle maker tho? Kappa
zetleri: roborock?
JonThomasK: the AI on them sucks.. at least the one i bought
brbdontdie: damn that was way better
mutrx: monkaHmm https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU monkaHmm https://imgur.com/UEgRKwU
georgehotz: https://github.com/commaai/cereal
Tarzeuss: Two days of Streams in a row? Thanks man you are awesome for doing this!
Thealvisz: I WANT BOTH ;_;
mutrx: trying to partner
aa_ato: no
itsChoudhry: @georgehotz What if I offer you a waffle maker for a picutre?? deal??
Artara_: how about taking a picture with the waffle maker, but I don't need it
thundershots999: I only photograph lightning
logi6000: so will he just carry the waffle maker everywhere just in case
anup_kodlekere: what you cookin
7Locrian7: :)
CianKy: yo yo @georgehotz have you ever used prolog before?
Thealvisz: Imma sell it to scrap
Thealvisz: Kappa
braininavatt: can you write some documentation on the rules on getting the waffle maker? Kappa
thundershots999: that coffee maker is LOUD
7Locrian7: george you have no emotes
braininavatt: ^
7Locrian7: what the heck
knilecrack: who needs emotes
7Locrian7: FeelsBadMan i do
zetleri: ruyuHot
thundershots999: I can hear that coffee maker in Connecticut
logi6000: is @adibaby04 even here anymore
logi6000: @thundershots999 oof
JonThomasK: that brewing is loud
itsChoudhry: Make a model which generates emotes with GANs
thundershots999: that oven has to be pre heated
chelsiquixote: where's your bud light?
thundershots999: Don't burn the mother down
logi6000: what kind of fucking back to the Future oven do you have then @thundershots999
thundershots999: Its a wolf oven
logi6000: hmm
ktzkalash: when u gonna do another xmas special?
logi6000: has anyone crashed using openpilot?
forkdb: I think he is making use of that oven for deep learning purposes, hence, the noise... hehe
logi6000: @forkdb makes sense
7Locrian7: he's not looking, i'm gonna say it:
7Locrian7: penis
logi6000: tendies!
7Locrian7: no
logi6000: @7locrian7 you said a no no wors
sirleeroyjenkins: 4 hours
itsChoudhry: 69 mins
JonThomasK: Ask Alexa
Darvein21: 1337 mins
brbdontdie: at least a day
logi6000: 42069 seconds
robby0313: Until they are cooked
JonThomasK: You have Alexa.. ask her. She smart
raulciuntastefan: Kappa
vtcN_: 1 minute at a million degrees
logi6000: until 4/20/69
zetleri: u can take it out when its 1576464579
veomx: hey bros
sirleeroyjenkins: u read it wrong it says 13-17 hours not minutes. Make sure u cook it thoroghly wouldnt wanna eat raw chicken
thundershots999: 7.8 x 1011 Nanoseconds
dahlenn1: dahlenn1 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
raulciuntastefan: is coffee good ?
raulciuntastefan: (dumb question)
raulciuntastefan: last time i drink was 2-3 yrs ago
logi6000: @raulciuntastefan no question is dumb unless it is dumb
sirleeroyjenkins: if u like bitter things that give u energy
logi6000: drink tea or take CBD
adibaby04: im back boyz
logi6000: the 15 yr old used to be intern
adibaby04: si si now in school
raulciuntastefan: thx boyz
logi6000: CBD the best option if you want good night's sleep
adibaby04: i want a github revieww
presidentkanyewest2024: what keyboard do you use?
logi6000: take one small edibal and you out in a hour
thundershots999: now I want a cinnamon roll
adibaby04: now i want a github review
logi6000: @georgehotz will you mail me a cinnamon roll
adibaby04: https://github.com/adiprerepa
adibaby04: YIPPEE
adibaby04: dont roast me
krouzux: >java
raulciuntastefan: u from India ?
cold_ali: lmfao
raulciuntastefan: Kappa
tsAllySparkles: https://github.com/askalice
gseven_: ahahah
adibaby04: nah
Tastydrol: haha
JonThomasK: java WutFace
adibaby04: NOOO
presidentkanyewest2024: J LUL V LUL
THX1342: LUL
itsChoudhry: Fuck me up fam https://github.com/ItsChoudhry
knilecrack: ahahaha
adibaby04: i know it so well
adibaby04: not fair
sirleeroyjenkins: wow very thorough github review
thundershots999: I drink my coffee black with 15 sugars
raulciuntastefan: this lad is for sure from India
adibaby04: go into the code tho
adibaby04: its coooool
Th3G4mingbros: xD
cold_ali: why not learn java?
ffntdt: why
adibaby04: ok
adibaby04: go into the go
Jeppelelle: Doing adventure of code today?
forkdb: Why is java bad ... George?
logi6000: because Java is going to be dead soon
forkdb: Please explain
tsAllySparkles: tsAllySparkles subscribed at Tier 1.
XiuYee1: Hello
adibaby04: too verbose
tsAllySparkles: there
sirleeroyjenkins: george just roasted this man for using a programming language that he isnt a fan of
tsAllySparkles: https://github.com/askalice
adibaby04: i personally dont like it but i know it so well
zetleri: 2h till AOC?
JonThomasK: PHP WutFace
cold_ali: i wish i could use vim like that lol
michaelmaier007: woke up this this stream
logi6000: @georgehotz ts Ally sparkles subed do the review
thundershots999: i'm still trying to master if then else in basic
zetleri: front-end .. yikes
JonThomasK: php and javascript. the two worst choices
Imeriall: What language should we learn then? Most universities teach Java nowadays.
tsAllySparkles: lmao
Imeriall: in intro classes
sirleeroyjenkins: just use Rust
forkdb: Why not java .. please explain
JonThomasK: time to do acid
gseven_: python and go
knilecrack: ahaha
braininavatt: trippy
peter35_: ocaml
cold_ali: dope AF
hardtarget4: trying not to have a seizure rn
sirleeroyjenkins: Toontown was a great game
tsAllySparkles: those commits are all me
tsAllySparkles: i changed my github name
logi6000: @jonthomask ikr
tsAllySparkles: webgl
JonThomasK: dances
sirleeroyjenkins: is that what u used for the fractals thingy
420lokki69: LUL
420lokki69: good tune
THX1342: trippy
tsAllySparkles: add axes
tsAllySparkles: dat.gui
camidon: take some LSD
tsAllySparkles: i could help with that
vexedkiller0071: *LCD
logi6000: hire her for web
adibaby04: this one is the coolest one inpired by you: https://github.com/adiprerepa/Car-Rpc
tsAllySparkles: lol
forkdb: George... please tell us why not to learn and use java?!...
tsAllySparkles: give me a better salary then maybe lol
JonThomasK: because better things exist
tsAllySparkles: if you use mapbox for your mapping engine
tsAllySparkles: then i can integrate three into that i've done it before
raulciuntastefan: yes dude , u gotta tell us why u dont like java
ffntdt: why not java? im learning to do android right now lol
raulciuntastefan: u cant escape that easily
adibaby04: this ones cool: https://github.com/adiprerepa/Car-Rpc
krouzux: anything OOP related just stay away
adibaby04: @krouzux so no C ? thats wrong
oMythra: forces oop and slow there you go @forkdb
krouzux: uh you can program in C without using OOP
krouzux: I do it everyday
THX1342: LUL
oMythra: exactly @krouzux
adibaby04: ic
braininavatt: rip
krouzux: its like a subset of C that is just C
thundershots999: Java and Maroon 5 FTW
krouzux: C with function & operator overloading
THX1342: adibaby04 it's very professional and impressive for a 15yo honestly.. nice job
adibaby04: woe ty
forkdb: Tell us why not to learn and work on java?
sirleeroyjenkins: Way to put down a 15year old for using Java
THX1342: but it's java...
THX1342: LUL
knilecrack: java is good
jo_renttt: I just got here why stay away from OOP? @krouzux
krouzux: i mean better to learn now than late
krouzux: because it has no relevance to actually programming
oMythra: not stay away from oop just use it only when necessary
THX1342: leave java for when you need to work in a 1000 person development team for a monolithic bank
adibaby04: yea im trying to move to golang
tsAllySparkles: it's not hard
tsAllySparkles: three.js buffer geometry makes it really easy to make a lot of stuff performant
logi6000: if I sub will you mail me a cinna roll. plz hook me up.
oMythra: go is cool @adibaby04
1monkjuice: dp > oop
adibaby04: agreed @oMythra
tsAllySparkles: https://threejs.org/examples/webgl_buffergeometry_instancing_billboards.html
Jeppelelle: George must have a mouth made of iron, eating pasta when its on fire and cinema rolls straight out of the owen
itsChoudhry: Wait you use Qt for your tools now????
tsAllySparkles: https://threejs.org/examples/webgl_buffergeometry_uint.html
adibaby04: fix this repo: https://github.com/adiprerepa/grpc-go-chat-server its not working lmao
michaelmaier007: dont eat too much :) stay in shape
tsAllySparkles: very performant
jo_renttt: Why do they only teach me OOP in college
logi6000: if I sub will you mail me a cinna roll. plz hook me up
tsAllySparkles: that plus VideoTexture
raulciuntastefan: is that a donut ?
tsAllySparkles: yeah but it's far less documented
tsAllySparkles: no the menus are dat.gui.js
tsAllySparkles: https://github.com/dataarts/dat.gui
tsAllySparkles: yeah it's amazing, and super easy to use
tsAllySparkles: ctrl enter
JonThomasK: run
logi6000: the best web dev I can do is if you set me up with a bootstrap template
Latyos: top left corner run
adibaby04: fix this repo: https://github.com/adiprerepa/grpc-go-chat-server its not working lmao
tsAllySparkles: oh maybe not
tsAllySparkles: thought that would run
adibaby04: js weird
tsAllySparkles: maybe cmd tner?
tsAllySparkles: enter*
knilecrack: yeah
itsChoudhry: itsChoudhry subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak! aaayyy
Imeriall: Thanks for the HahaBall @itschoudhry
pouringhotteaonyourface: did you cook your own meal?
sirleeroyjenkins: if u have milk dip em in milk
sirleeroyjenkins: bomb af
MiniManiacBlob: g'day George
guy_ross: guy_ross is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 8 in the channel!
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to 1monkjuice!
guy_ross: guy_ross's Gift shared rewards to 5 others in Chat!
logi6000: thx subs!
adibaby04: ty subs
1monkjuice: yee, support
guy_ross: ;)
420lokki69: ty for sub
sirleeroyjenkins: lookin a little charred on the bottom
krouzux: lets see it again
Nudethedder: pajaKek
adibaby04: i got revenue
THX1342: @logi6000 thx no subs :(
ProfessorMagikarp0: those were the good days
420lokki69: you need some coffee with that
ffntdt: so wtf did i just learn in 2 years in university? they only teach oop lol
bravech: are you not allowed to show revenue or is it just not socially acceptible
brbdontdie: what is the consensus on typing with sticky fingers?
adibaby04: just side projects @ffntdt
tsAllySparkles: https://mrdoob.neocities.org/017/
krouzux: uni is not for knowledge but a certificate saying you "know" shit
itsChoudhry: Nah I just removed all my good projects off my github because apparently I had offensive comments and employers don't like that. I need to spice up my github
tsAllySparkles: https://thebookofshaders.com/
METH_HEAD_MIKE: DESCRIBE TASTE DansGame
brbdontdie: @krouzux hey man, some people can really explore their interests in university
logi6000: why don't we rename stream to binging that part of the web
jo_renttt: @ffntdt thats what IM saying
brbdontdie: I would never have gotten into computers because I used to think that it was too hard as a hobby
stoogethomas: yo it's geohot and for those that don't know I'm getting sued by sony
krouzux: @brbdontdie related to software development careers that is
adibaby04: i want an un-roast
Latyos: Hey, do you have your vim config uploaded anywhere?
adibaby04: go review
adibaby04: golang*
MiniManiacBlob: so what is the task right now?
sirleeroyjenkins: make a btc miner disguised as shaders
bravech: uni is good for connections
logi6000: @stoogethomas let's take it out of the court room and in to the streets
raulciuntastefan: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b74GiMB08UE&list=PLiDow_mvyEAtyVEOHAmokrZh0GdV8wt8y
raulciuntastefan: dont ban me
stoogethomas: @logi6000 ;)
raulciuntastefan: pls
THX1342: https://twitter.com/hexpwn/status/1206345584631844864
oMythra: its good to learn oop just gotta know when to apply it and when not too
erichtp: sketch.io time PogChamp
braininavatt: LUL
美國威傅後援會會長: LUL
METH_HEAD_MIKE: BAN HIM 😡
p4ri: your so smart man
sirleeroyjenkins: hows the burnt ass cinnamon buns
bravech: @jo_renttt don't not learn something bc some stranger on the internet told you not to
logi6000: @meth_head_mike wtf is your username
tsAllySparkles: hit the examples tab
tsAllySparkles: on the docs
THlAG0: https://www.shadertoy.com/view/ttXGWH
THlAG0: see this
adibaby04: GOLANG REVIEWWW
METH_HEAD_MIKE: PogChamp
METH_HEAD_MIKE: NEW HALO PogChamp
braininavatt: smooooth Kreygasm
stoogethomas: will you play half life vr?
oMythra: make half life 3
sirleeroyjenkins: because u burnt the shit out of them
logi6000: mail me a cinna roll. plz hook me up
logi6000: ayy I got the quest
cloakW: quest is beginners VR
brbdontdie: @krouzux I don't know if i necessarily agree with that
stoogethomas: honest question I've always wondered how you have so much energy. do you supplement or are you just generally a beast in life
jo_renttt: Its not that its just that its the first time I heard of this @bravech
adibaby04: ill shut up when i get a golang review
michaelmaier007: what time is it there?.
logi6000: I got it bc I'm not a big gamer but I like gaming
knilecrack: PC gaming is not dead
stoogethomas: hahahaha
imsuperficial: LUL LUL
erichtp: LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: same
bravech: quest is good if you don't have a pc powerful enough
camidon: word
sirleeroyjenkins: primeagenBuild primeagenBuild Adderall for sure
cloakW: PC gaming is more alive than its ever been lmao
1monkjuice: WutFace
raulciuntastefan: cocaine is actually great
METH_HEAD_MIKE: Same FeelsGoodMan
HexaField: hey george how are you today? :)
raulciuntastefan: Kappa
METH_HEAD_MIKE: Kappa
jo_renttt: Kapp
bravech: mobile gaming is a different market from pc gaming
logi6000: do you have adhd?
bravech: more casual
tsAllySparkles: lmao
peter35_: i miss adderall FeelsBadMan
forkdb: Tell us why not to learn java...
brbdontdie: I don't think you that university will teach you everything that you need to know (not even close) but they introduce some pretty heavy concepts that the old me would never had touched if it wasn't needed to get my degree
bravech: ^^^
sirleeroyjenkins: then u just switch to coke and its alot better
raulciuntastefan: *need more adderall
krouzux: or you could've learned online for free
krouzux: or bought some books
bravech: uni won't spit you out ready to get a job; you've gotta do that yourself
logi6000: snorts Adderall
ProfessorMagikarp0: homeostasis or something? monkaS
raulciuntastefan: tolerance is a hoe
adibaby04: GOLANG REVIIIIIEEEWWW
knilecrack: exactly
ProfessorMagikarp0: so not being urself for a bit helps LUL
moonify: @georgehotz What about lsd-microdosis?
sirleeroyjenkins: lmaooo so true
lua_320: @krouzux or you can pirate books and buy them if you think is worth it
JonThomasK: i organized my email
logi6000: @georgehotz do you ever just smoke straight CBD flower
ProfessorMagikarp0: dont get ban monkaS
cloakW: CiGrip
JonThomasK: coke?
stoogethomas: I was talking about vitamins not supplements just saying hahaha Just so much respect for the focus and energy you have.
brbdontdie: yeah but @krouzux most people are not disciplined enough to actually self-learn consistently
adibaby04: GOLANG
adibaby04: what about coke
J3rwin: @brbdontdie true
brbdontdie: I think once you have developed an interest in the material, it becomes easier.
moonify: @JonThomasK Coke Bad, psycho good
bravech: there's a whole lawsuit going on because putting CBD in foods is illegal
Artara_: what's the impulse to decide to take adderall?
adibaby04: almost???????????????????????????/?
cloakW: "almost" LULW
METH_HEAD_MIKE: Kappa
krouzux: comma dispensary when?
knilecrack: what is that drink?
lua_320: Yes, it's easier to learn something you like
logi6000: so did you take coke ever?
michaelmaier007: its coffee
ProfessorMagikarp0: nickiG drugs are bad mmmmmmkay
bravech: meth is bad
stoogethomas: meth is bad kids
jo_renttt: LUL
erichtp: heroine is the wave
adibaby04: heroin?
lua_320: krokodile is the best drug in existence
JonThomasK: sugar?
jax05_: exactly
brbdontdie: I used to think that I needed adderall, but I just needed coffee
MiniManiacBlob: anything worth taking to actually get work done? @georgehotz
jo_renttt: Nitrous oxide
camidon: melamine is fun
logi6000: he never mentioned heroin
camidon: ketamine
bravech: dopamine is a drug, man
cloakW: Kappa
THX1342: one of the worst is tabacco
logi6000: he done fucked up
raulciuntastefan: lsd is great
brbdontdie: I have never tried adderall, but coffee did the trick for me
stoogethomas: meth just destroys your dopamine though
ProfessorMagikarp0: bath salt nickiG zombies
bravech: george check out r/meth
MiniManiacBlob: sugar is the worst bois
mdrake_: yep, I've known some functioning meth addicts
dahlenn1: flakka is the best
Artara_: I'm not addicted to cocaine I just like how it smells
l33tkr3w: Opioids super hard to escape
forkdb: For gods sake .. please tell us why not to learn java George... we are all still waiting...
logi6000: @georgehotz so have you ever tried coke
adibaby04: ^^
death_gadget: Ice is the real killer
brbdontdie: do you drink soda after meals during work?
raulciuntastefan: LUL
michaelmaier007: @artara_ thats the point...
knilecrack: white horse
bravech: there's some people on r/meth who've gone 6 months normal but they all eventually break down
l33tkr3w: Buprenephrine is icky icky icky
jax05_: freakin tea, coffee, and sugar
THX1342: forkdb why do you want validation so bad?! LUL if you like it, thats good for you
jax05_: worst of the drugs
Jeppelelle: DMT?
MiniManiacBlob: benzos are fucked
forkdb: For gods sake .. please tell us why not to learn java George... we are all still waiting...
logi6000: so have you ever tried coke
adibaby04: golang review?
THX1342: imo tobacco is the worst
knilecrack: especially in USA
bravech: asking george why not is noob thinking
ProfessorMagikarp0: any ice chewing relapse ?
jax05_: I think benzos are overhyped
ProfessorMagikarp0: Kappa
knilecrack: you guys put sugar in everything
1monkjuice: im surrounded by 3 cans of coke, 2 bottles, 1 can of speed and 3gs of weed
bravech: sugar ice relapse
stoogethomas: for legal purposes he means cola
adibaby04: GOLANGG
MiniManiacBlob: @georgehotz but im forced to learn java at college (uk college)
brbdontdie: what's wrong with chewing ice?
Waywoah: bad for your teeth
l33tkr3w: Micro fracture teeth
stoogethomas: java is the gateway to c
bravech: lmao
J3rwin: jesus
kingkong3211: @MiniManiacBlob same man
brbdontdie: oh man, I chew ice and give me dog ice all the time
METH_HEAD_MIKE: Kappa
brbdontdie: big yikes
gseven_: be careful with what you say @georgehotz twitch is savage
ProfessorMagikarp0: fbi open up monkaS
美國威傅後援會會長: Kappa
tsAllySparkles: oof
jo_renttt: TOS
bravech: tv normalizes drug use
MiniManiacBlob: @kingkong3211 it is kinda shit but i understand its uses and purpose
peter35_: freud was a huge coke addict
raulciuntastefan: cocaine isnt even that great
stoogethomas: java is the gateway drug to c . c is the gateway drug to c
raulciuntastefan: to pricey
michaelmaier007: i saw a guy here in germany. i seriously thought that was you. And unfortunately ofc itwasnt you :(
JonThomasK: musk
tsAllySparkles: there totally are people who do that
tsAllySparkles: my cousin did that
jo_renttt: r/meth
THX1342: coke is like alcohol x 1000
bravech: python & c are the true power couple
forkdb: I work in one of those big java vendor companies... so, tell me why we shoul not work on java...
oMythra: it aint that serious bro @forkdb
jo_renttt: LUL @forkdb
adibaby04: javas just stupid
knilecrack: you die on coke very fast
adibaby04: too verbose
logi6000: so here's the thing he never said he never did heroin
moonify: @adibaby04 agree
Artara_: he wants to give away his waffle maker cause that's where he stores his coke.. don't fall for it guys
adibaby04: I agree that java sucks but i know it so well
ProfessorMagikarp0: doesnt linus torvalds hate Java too LUL
raulciuntastefan: george is actually working with the dea
raulciuntastefan: dea
tomcroose: @trainwreckstb
bravech: java and nvidia are the devil
adibaby04: not much i can do
cloakW: squadW @tomcroose
Riqour: squadW
logi6000: @bravech and intel
cloakW: 🦍
stoogethomas: it's upside down
wc_dozer: A cure for Java is Scala, slightly less horrible syntax, same JWM
stoogethomas: yeah
JonThomasK: lol
Riqour: its a rectangle
l33tkr3w: your monitor is upside down
stoogethomas: lol rip
moonify: 360
THX1342: australian car?
jo_renttt: Rotate display
kingkong3211: lol
zetleri: and mirrored?
tsAllySparkles: lmao
yunk3r: Region Australia?
sirleeroyjenkins: What exactly is this Openpilot thing
tsAllySparkles: threejs would be better for this shit
JonThomasK: turn your monitor right side up
raulciuntastefan: rotate display LUL
tsAllySparkles: tbh tho
ProfessorMagikarp0: nickiThink ur debugger build in Australia?
bravech: stiffness
cloakW: membrane keyboards hurt my ears
adibaby04: GO
adibaby04: REVIEW
l33tkr3w: why is the simulation 0.3 fps
Artara_: is it emulating a retina?
michaelmaier007: @cloakw but they are statisfying
logi6000: you got a citation for having weed in Texas?
Riqour: what ide is that
adibaby04: its vim
Riqour: ah
JonThomasK: its not an ide
Riqour: text editor right?
kingkong3211: its an editor
jo_renttt: yes
sirleeroyjenkins: I recommend chicken tendies
peter35_: FeelsGoodMan
stoogethomas: Why are you doing this when you could be hacking crypto exchanges. 1 exchange had 50mil stolen last week. That could be you
stoogethomas: lol
logi6000: @georgehotz you got a citation for having weed in Texas? don't you have a medical card
stoogethomas: sorry last month
bravech: RIP vod
JonThomasK: kanye west?
sirleeroyjenkins: how do u know it wasnt him @stoogethomas
SheitanasGM: Where ur not
MiniManiacBlob: anyone have any advice on ways of improving your coding skills fast?
stoogethomas: haha
adibaby04: this will get stuck in ur head
rkxbz: is that oxxymiron?
adibaby04: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q3cFtBx4jRE
rkxbz: where did you found it @georgehotz ?
ProfessorMagikarp0: KKomrade
Riqour: @MiniManiacBlob work on projects so you put your knowledge to use
raulciuntastefan: is that russian ?
METH_HEAD_MIKE: nice audio FeelsGoodMan
JjohnConstantine: нот бад)
SheitanasGM: If U like Russian Rap u need listen Miyagi
rkxbz: @raulciuntastefan yep
Still2050: Wtf
logi6000: George hotz how easy is it to get a medical card
MiniManiacBlob: @Riqour what kind of projects
Adolfich: ебать
trev0rk911: @georgehotz have you tried tianeptine?
ProfessorMagikarp0: welcome comrades
MiniManiacBlob: @Riqour you mean larger scale tasks?
moonify: are you streaming advent today?
JjohnConstantine: неожиданно)
dmitry_ra: Вот это поворот
Adolfich: зашквар так то
sirleeroyjenkins: cyka blyatski
Riqour: @MiniManiacBlob anything. You can google small to big project ideas
adibaby04: yea
gseven_: CURVA
adibaby04: do projects
MiniManiacBlob: @Riqour ye ok
MiniManiacBlob: @Riqour thx
oMythra: putin be rockin to this
SheitanasGM: dobre vicher
THX1342: cheeky breeky
mrigor: osujdau
sirleeroyjenkins: geohot Russian hacker confirmed
michaelmaier007: he sounds a little bit like eminem.
Immortalsamurai_: anyone you have any good laptop recommendations? need to buy a new one soon
oMythra: for windows: xps 15 and x1 carbon @Immortalsamurai_
THX1342: @Immortalsamurai_ XPS
1monkjuice: theres already plenty of research for that in the web @Immortalsamurai_
oMythra: can install linux on mem too
adibaby04: @georgehotz can we do more github reviews?
trev0rk911: why aren't there more programmer streamers on twitch?
adibaby04: ^^
bankzed: there
guy_ross: can i send ya one?
oMythra: there are check out science and tech section
adibaby04: i kind of want to start streaming programming my projects
bankzed: whadup from another RIT dropout
logi6000: why are we listening to Russian shit
Immortalsamurai_: @thx1342 @omythra thanks!
stoogethomas: does it matter the language
rkxbz: @logi6000 that is not shit man
METH_HEAD_MIKE: DansGame YOU DONT SKIP
jo_renttt: never need a bitch
raulciuntastefan: thats garbage indeed
JonThomasK: as you bob your head to it
bankzed: check out some Higher Brother, some OP Chinese Rap
bravech: george can you play your rap
logi6000: listen to JID or something lyrical
bankzed: he's Canadian, so doesn't count
THX1342: LUL
JjohnConstantine: Kappa
raulciuntastefan: Kappa
treestompztv: BARS TriHard
JonThomasK: lol
tsAllySparkles: do you make music?
raulciuntastefan: lmao
mazsociety: random word generator
Artara_: 200iq
ProfessorMagikarp0: we need emo kid rap nickiG
vtcN_: LUL
braininavatt: modern poet Kappa
jo_renttt: sonically
jo_renttt: pleasing
oMythra: cockpit out there flying on its own
michaelmaier007: linkin park is awesome too.
l33tkr3w: gotta compare to top 100 right now in rus
peter35_: russians are like effortlessly poetic in their prose it seems
logi6000: linkin park or green day or JID or something good
l33tkr3w: more poetic
bankzed: Russian rap is good as long as it's subverting Putin
tsAllySparkles: https://emu.bz/winXP.mp3
JonThomasK: go back to pocket pussy
adibaby04: Listen to this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q3cFtBx4jRE
oMythra: you sure Tolstoy didnt write that
mrigor: easier to rhyme with conjugation IMO (russian)
logi6000: listen to this https://youtu.be/oZgNcLoZLjE
METH_HEAD_MIKE: KKona WTF
jo_renttt: nobody LUL
CraftyGaming: There is great american rap....it is no longer what the mainstream wants to hear. It's quite sad
veomx: :D
gseven_: POET
jo_renttt: what about blinding lights? @georgehotz
JonThomasK: doesnt even make sense
bankzed: the best art is stolen
trev0rk911: @georgehotz are you into nootropics?
bravech: @mrigor I only have experience with spanish, but isn't rhyming same-ended verbs repetitive?
jo_renttt: Old weeknd PogChamp
bankzed: it's not just the drugs, it's also Gigi Hadid.
bravech: kinda as if you rhymed the same word with itself
jo_renttt: and selena LUL @bankzed
Xplouder: listen some joyner lucas's music
jo_renttt: Pass
michaelmaier007: its f...ing monday again....
adibaby04: yeah
adibaby04: joyner lucas
whoishenry123: the way the weeknd sings it makes it sound cool
bravech: george have you listened to to pimp a butterfly
mazsociety: or just listen to 21 savage and then you don't have to worry about understanding any of the words
braininavatt: cant relate Kappa
dahlenn1: jonyer lucas is lit
mrigor: @bravech pushkin is the most famous poet I believe and its all ending rhymes http://www.poetryloverspage.com/poets/pushkin/pushkin_ind.html
vexedkiller0071: anyone listen arctic monkeys (old)
veomx: marshall mathers lp
logi6000: let's listen to juice wrld in memorizarion. he's not great but I mean. he dead now
michaelmaier007: listen to linkin park im sure you'll like it.
JjohnConstantine: MC georgehotz
THX1342: vexedkiller0071 ye
moonify: the message bro
logi6000: green day minority. you would love that song
adibaby04: github
adibaby04: review
mazsociety: have you listened to the new joyner lucas song?
jo_renttt: Do you like kendrick?
bravech: seizure most likely related to drugs
jo_renttt: a fukin seizure.......
bravech: heavy use of lean
slipperrybunz: tried to hide drugs by swallowing them
Xplouder: hopsin - ill mind of hopsin 7 is lit
hardtarget4: percocet
whoishenry123: only the weeknd can make his lyrics sound good
J3rwin: rofl
logi6000: @xplouder true true
bankzed: the hip hop police killed Juice WRLD
hardtarget4: rip lil peep
sirleeroyjenkins: Seizure likely due to withdrawal from Xanax
ukluke12: rip the goat
adibaby04: GIHUB REVIEW
trev0rk911: imagine if Elon started streaming on twitch regularly?
mazsociety: joyner lucas - revenge intro
bravech: hmm he'd rather die than go to prison I guess
Artara_: when was the last time you listened to kaiyko
hardtarget4: emo rap will never be the same
michaelmaier007: linkin park is awesome too
THX1342: https://youtu.be/Da04TlloTg0 good brazilian rap
logi6000: he killed himself and he wanted to be the highest he had ever been
bravech: @mrigor thanks for the link
sirleeroyjenkins: just dont do opiates lol
trev0rk911: or use kratom, shit works well and is legal
peter35_: grow opium poppies Kappa
logi6000: yo lil barnacle. let's listen to him
JonThomasK: rofl
mutrx: are we doing music suggestions?
krouzux: what is this
mutrx: https://soundcloud.com/whatsonot/trust-plastic-plates-remix-16bit-44khz
tsAllySparkles: @adibaby04 what github review?
ProfessorMagikarp0: geo living his best life LUL
jo_renttt: how bout travis scott? @georgehotz
duzy: lool
trev0rk911: stay away from kratom extracts with kratom leaf, shit actually gets you high
tsAllySparkles: https://soundcloud.com/allysparkles/desire
knilecrack: did you ever listen to 90's rap?
adibaby04: george golang review
logi6000: minority green day plz
mrigor: @georgehotz jon hopkins is good 'flow' background coding artist
adibaby04: @tsAllySparkles in general
adibaby04: roasting bro
mutrx: https://soundcloud.com/jew3lz/look-at-me-now
bravech: george have you heard of Alltta?
logi6000: is it the coffee or the coke in the waffle maker
trev0rk911: white maeng da kratom 10 grams with legal weed perfect combo, how long until cocaine is legalized in the united states?
death_gadget: Run The Jewels!!
michaelmaier007: water is the best drug.
mutrx: https://soundcloud.com/whatsonot/trust-plastic-plates-remix-16bit-44khz
hardtarget4: alright. lets work
logi6000: CBD the bomb
vexedkiller0071: gayhiphop for good lyrics
grey_street: what's this song
vexedkiller0071: cummo
bravech: @vexedkiller0071 https://soundcloud.com/kaiyko
bravech: @grey_street https://soundcloud.com/kaiyko
bravech: sorry wrong person
grey_street: thanks
vexedkiller0071: all cool lol
logi6000: intense coding begins
trev0rk911: tianeptine is also another synthetic opiate that I've found to be very euphoric. Crazy that it's still legal and easy to verify that it's not laced because it's extremely hygroscopic, and it reacts with mandelin reagent in a very unique way.
mutrx: https://soundcloud.com/whatsonot/trust-plastic-plates-remix-16bit-44khz
adibaby04: signing off for the night, gotta grind an english essay by tomorrow, fuking high school
Riqour: @trev0rk911 whats it like, I've never tried opiates
logi6000: I have a fucking social studies test tommorow 100 pts but I should be good. I got a sleeping problem anyway
mutrx: doing honours next year :)
hardtarget4: lol
dontbeameme: Let’s gooooo
bankzed: Haha, stay in school kids
dontbeameme: Let’s get this problem solv3d
logi6000: @bankzed what is I start a million dollar company
tsAllySparkles: roast my music tho https://soundcloud.com/allysparkles/desire
bravech: george you know what's better than opiates
bravech: trading options on robinhood
dontbeameme: xbox series x let’s go jail break it
tsAllySparkles: i liked your rap
logi6000: @bravech that shit fucking garbage
tsAllySparkles: sony rap lol
bankzed: Is this jeopardy? Are you answering a question in form of a question? You proved my point, stay in school. s/is/if
shivoshifter: @georgehotz Hey explain me that paradoxon, as soon as we have real artificial intelligence. Wouldn't she have understood our 3D world within miliseconds? And move on to the 4 Dimension and so on ...
knilecrack: @tsAllySparkles why twitter says pronstar?
dontbeameme: AI will become autonomous and evolve into something else
tsAllySparkles: don't worry about it that's out of scope
JjohnConstantine: haw many cups of coffee do you drink a day ?
mrigor: @georgehotz why add commit instead of commit -am?
dontbeameme: I don’t want AI to take over
Artara_: he drinks all of them
dontbeameme: We don’t have the tech to fight off the robots
logi6000: @dontbeameme you might just be out of luck
michaelmaier007: @jjohnconstantine 74
JjohnConstantine: Kappa
dontbeameme: @logi6000 Elon musk made the best point that a computer literally learned any game and could win by just typing in the game rules
logi6000: hmmm
mutrx: g emo hots
trev0rk911: @Riqour extremely short high, 35-minute rush, has a stimulant effect after the rush, just can't shut up. 100 mg for recreational dose. Don't go over 500mg in a day becasue there are some studies that hypothesize that it might be toxic at larger doses due to amineptine (a derivative) being well established as toxic to the liver at doses higher than 100mg
bankzed: That reminds me of Check out XavierWulf on #SoundCloud
dontbeameme: @logi6000 If AI takes over, they will be roaches
logi6000: elon also said that we don't need driver monitoring. nah he is still a genius
bankzed: Err copy and paste fail
prakyath_kantharaju: what do you think about the vscode after using it for a few streams?
Riqour: LOL
stoogethomas: lol
bankzed: VS Code is bloated, use VIM
mutrx: asprin
dontbeameme: Lolololol 100mg you dead
logi6000: CBD maybe?
ProfessorMagikarp0: 100mg? taking dosage advice from lil peep Kappa
mutrx: you can take inf CBD
dontbeameme: Rip juice
Riqour: dude was about to kill me :(
raulciuntastefan: LUL
Riqour: Kappa
shivoshifter: @georgehotz Hey explain me that paradoxon, as soon as we have real artificial intelligence. Wouldn't she have understood our 3D world within miliseconds? And move on to the 4 Dimension and so on ...
mutrx: Kappa
bravech: has anybody studied cbd closely
jo_renttt: Was that a Kapp on 100 THC
mrigor: hes bad at converting to metric
logi6000: don't test that tolorence either
dontbeameme: Why can we just put confidence in a bottle
mutrx: did you guys ever watch a fuck ton of Air Crash Investigation?
tohsdnilb: Mushrooms
tsAllySparkles: what is an IMU?
bravech: inertial measurement unit
jo_renttt: monkaS
mutrx: how was the coffee
thecprogramminglanguage: monkaS
logi6000: it's the monkeys
bravech: don't worry it's just a bit
michaelmaier007: try a song from linkin park.
mutrx: that airbus long LUL
sirleeroyjenkins: geohot terrorist confirmed
knilecrack: I read the article that you posted a while ago about boeing
logi6000: someting Wong Wei too low ho Lee fuk bang ding ow
jo_renttt: on watch list now
bankzed: I've modelled an IMU in MATLAB before for a drone project
erichtp: where did Malaysia 370 go
mutrx: @logi6000 that was legendary
bravech: @georgehotz https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2019/05/the-radio-navigation-planes-use-to-land-safely-is-insecure-and-can-be-hacked/
bravech: hacking planes
veomx: Lufthansa is also nice
logi6000: @mutrx ikr
METH_HEAD_MIKE: monkaS
mutrx: what's the worst way to die, plane crash or overdose Kappa
bravech: plane crash definitely
veomx: very nice
mutrx: overdose ya
krouzux: chicken rolls?
logi6000: plane crash. at least you get high
raulciuntastefan: listening mumble rap while od
mutrx: @logi6000 LUL
bankzed: I heard it was hijacked by 👽
bankzed: Kappa
ProfessorMagikarp0: thats pretty fucking metal, i respect it
bravech: gotta book seats in the back so you're more likely to live
michaelmaier007: ho lee fuk... sounds interesting.
krouzux: just appeared out of no where
erichtp: so when are you gonna take flying lessons
oMythra: run to the tail it usually breaks off
peter35_: that german pilot who flew into a mountain monkaS
logi6000: https://youtu.be/k-GEhArUuZ8 @georgehotz thank me later
mutrx: the one that let a kid fly the plane
bankzed: Yes, right by the wings
mutrx: best condom commercial ever
knilecrack: @logi6000 AHAHAHAHAHAH
mutrx: @logi6000 best troll ever
logi6000: yup
Abnico: Wassup pimps
logi6000: get George to play on stream
bravech: est is best time zone
Artara_: @logi6000 LUL
Vjasal: @georgehotz what's this advent of code anyway
raulciuntastefan: LMAO that video
mutrx: @Vjasal google is pretty cool eh?
bravech: google it
tsAllySparkles: why not vscode?
tsAllySparkles: i don't understand how you can be so comfortable with vim
trev0rk911: the reason why you don't need to worry about tianeptine causing an overdose is that it doesn't cause a classical respiratory depression response like traditional full mu opioid agonists because of it having functional selectivity. I would be more worried that you would have a seizure if you overdosed but I doubt you would die. I've researched a bit and of course, I've used. It sort of has a ceiling type effect that being anxiety after you push past a certain point probably because it also releas
bravech: jetbrains suite vim plugin is the best
bankzed: bankzed subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! Check out https://popcorncomputer.com/
logi6000: https://youtu.be/k-GEhArUuZ8 @georgehotz I recommend you watch this video. this won't get you banned I promise on the waffle maker
mutrx: @trev0rk911 please call 911
trev0rk911: glutamate
logi6000: there goes another line
adibaby04: im back boyz plagarized an essay
PiroFloydian: hey streamer and chat first time here
bankzed: how about I promote usage of an SoC my buddy designs and builds?
mutrx: george do u know chubbyemu on youtube?
adibaby04: @georgehotz can i have a job
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCKOvOaJv4GK-oDqx-sj7VVg
raulciuntastefan: HeyGuys
P0LY: LULW
tsAllySparkles: college is such a cruel joke
PiroFloydian: do we always talk about substances here? also any thoughts on coding high? never tried it
logi6000: George you did make something of yourself.
bravech: oof doin my college essays rn
veomx: Dr. Georg
brickvo: @tsAllySparkles depends on what you do or if you know what you want to do
mutrx: is doing medicine worth it guys
Amammay: you ever eat a potato?
bankzed: yeah, I want those looking to do drugs instead buy computers such as this:
bankzed: https://popcorncomputer.com/
logi6000: @pirofloydian not always. he needs to smoke more weed on stream thi
adibaby04: @georgehotz i want a job pls
bankzed: computers >> drugs
adibaby04: ^^^
mutrx: @adibaby04 officially added to the blacklist
adibaby04: nOOO
adibaby04: nOw I caNt woRk at CoMa aI
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz did you always code from the terminal or was there a point where you switched to it? if you switched why and was there a hump to get over?
itsChoudhry: What's he doing right now?
mutrx: you need over 10k followers to join comma anyway
mrigor: @georgehotz terminal beep, make it stop :)
logi6000: and solve the speed challenge
tsAllySparkles: i have 18.9k followers, so i could probably join comma lol
tsAllySparkles: but idk about that speed challenge wat is it
JonThomasK: 1/2^2
adibaby04: @georgehotz whats ur vimrc?
tsAllySparkles: where?
Vegerot: !dotfiles
logi6000: gives you some training data and you have to find the speed of the car from a vid with ai.
trev0rk911: @mutrx No, I just checked my blood pressure it's 150/95 pulse 110. I don't do this very often only 3 times a week and I keep my doses under 500mg. I just have a lot of energy and I need to release it through typing, I have type racer up as well, trying to get my all time average over 95 wpm, almost there
Vegerot: !vimrc
tsAllySparkles: oh that.. yeah
bravech: @tsAllySparkles google it
tsAllySparkles: i saw that
bravech: oh nvm
tsAllySparkles: seems interesting
Vegerot: !r
mutrx: race me @trev0rk911
adibaby04: seems impossible
Vegerot: I give up lol
tsAllySparkles: can't be too hard
itssDK: itssDK subscribed with Twitch Prime.
tsAllySparkles: cv is weird tho
logi6000: @trev0rk911 do you need irl help I can give you some hotline numbers
mutrx: Thanks for the HahaHide @itssdk
tsAllySparkles: just gotta force yourself to learn how to interpolate data like that
tsAllySparkles: what gets me is understanding the scale of the objects on scene
adibaby04: YEAH
adibaby04: like i guess you would have to train a model to understand distances?
yyube_: is he using his local mac in terminal or is he sshd into a linux server?
ne3cross: Local
tsAllySparkles: sounds like some fun digging into openpilot
logi6000: did this guy really just say is he sshd
tsAllySparkles: im excited for my devkit to come
ne3cross: lol
mutrx: gemohots
braininavatt: Jebaited
dunehazard: arch for life
yyube_: what’s wrong with saying sshd?
ne3cross: That’s fair imo
mutrx: https://play.typeracer.com?rt=20ez1kqa8f
logi6000: that's the Damon for ssh
veomx: :D
logi6000: but George is excusing it on a Sunday night
bravech: dang it got 2nd place
mutrx: LUL
logi6000: @bravech for what
bravech: https://play.typeracer.com/?rt=20ez1kqa8f
trev0rk911: @logi6000 no man, like I said I know what a tia overdose feels like. Shakiness, dizziness and dry mouth. I've pushed it more than this before and survived. It brings headaches on but there are other tia addicts out there in taking 3 grams a day, I chat with them everyday on discord, we have are on little personal community, most of us, myself included addicted to opiates throughout our lvies
prakyath_kantharaju: Youtube video is demonetized for sure... LUL
ne3cross: Missing quotes
mutrx: LUL so many of chat are playing typeracer
logi6000: 18553391144 yo here's the drug abuse hotline have these guys on speed dial right next to 911 and probably your dealer
taxad0: what is ur zsh theme sir?
michaelmaier007: is that an imac pro?. or a macbook?.
bravech: tensorflow 3 when
logi6000: George rename backspace ai to pied piper
ne3cross: ne3cross subscribed at Tier 1.
Super_saiyan_3: did u try turning it off and on?
logi6000: George how did you get into coke
krouzux: AOC in 40mins
bankzed: F for Python 2
mufeedvh: F
dunehazard: F
adibaby04: @georgehotz cereal isnt letting me push a branch
logi6000: python 4 tho. semicolon at end
adibaby04: fuk ok
bankzed: We don't need no stinking seicolons
mutrx: @trev0rk911 is from r/ti
bankzed: *semicolon
mutrx: @trev0rk911 is from r/tianeptine
adibaby04: can i have read access
adibaby04: lmao
adibaby04: i jest
logi6000: @bankzed just sounds like something they would do like the print parentheses
braininavatt: lol
mutrx: @georgehotz race me whilst u wait
logi6000: how much longer is stream I got to go to sleep
bankzed: Nah, not as long as Guido is in charge
mufeedvh: it's morning here
adibaby04: @georgehotz once i finish the branch will you merge it?
bankzed: Watch the vod later, lol.
michaelmaier007: @logi6000 prolly 4h left
logi6000: oh great I'll probably fail my unit test tommorow
bankzed: Make a good pull request and he might merge it
logi6000: @trev0rk911 juice wrld
guy_ross: what a weird question.. @trev0rk911
michaelmaier007: @trev0rk911 your questions are creepy >(
logi6000: @michaelmaier007 true
mutrx: f
bravech: oof
searchingforlife: f
mdrake_: dang
moonify: F
lemonboxed: this is webmd chat
bankzed: F
knilecrack: seizure inc
Sim_Ayo: F
JjohnConstantine: F
michaelmaier007: i mean he was pushing the boundaries..
logi6000: ban topic is now medical advice I guess
mutrx: F for a failure in life for doing tianeptine
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz hey im new here. what's your story?
bankzed: HahaHide
ProfessorMagikarp0: nickiG it looks like u have a serious case of banned sir. its terminal
mutrx: @PiroFloydian LUL
P0LY: Kappa
mutrx: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
dunehazard: banned
bravech: google him
mutrx: LUL
mutrx: LUL LUL
mutrx: LUL LUL LUL
bravech: maximizing the micro-transportation of butter
mutrx: LUL LUL LUL LUL
mutrx: LUL
Sim_Ayo: why dont you just code an ai that programs this for u instead Kappa
mutrx: LUL LUL
mutrx: LUL
mdrake_: I use that same kind of butter
mutrx: LUL LUL LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: wow im so inspired now
roystang: wont the butter melt
bravech: bravech subscribed with Twitch Prime.
simmy7: is butter a code word for Coke?
dunehazard: Thanks for the HahaCat @bravech
roystang: woah
lemonboxed: not butter doesnt ever melt
ProfessorMagikarp0: butter is basically plastic LUL
braininavatt: wait what?
logi6000: the coke in the waffle maker
roystang: drugs are bad
mutrx: *checks his watch* no drugs
bankzed: Butter is code for Butter
bravech: HahaHide
PiroFloydian: oh lol i googled him
jadams: ratirlSad
searchingforlife: is your build failing cause of too much drugs
michaelmaier007: plot twist: that guy was fishing us.
braininavatt: george saving lives right there
Sim_Ayo: how can you see with that resolution scaling
bankzed: he had 911 in his name, clearly a cop
michaelmaier007: or whatever you would call it lol.
mutrx: @georgehotz should do the most complicated way to do 'hello world'
coppuh: that's for nixos isn't it lol
mrigor: @georgehotz why tf in c, thought py abstractions is what made it so good or is that only easy on google compute?
michaelmaier007: @bankzed yeah thats what i was thinkink lol :)
bankzed: @mutrx isn't that all code?
bravech: sounds like a pokemon
Sim_Ayo: is it really valuable to take the time to learn vim ?
krouzux: do you use mac at work as well?
mrigor: @Sim_Ayo yes
logi6000: remember the Joe Rogan army
bravech: vim doesn't take that long... use vimtutor
FaustPetrovich: @Sim_Ayo yes
Sim_Ayo: ok will try vim tutor ty
bankzed: vim will get you coding 100x faster, so yeah
mrigor: at least, i'm 200x faster
michaelmaier007: sorry for my f...ed up english. im from germany :(
bankzed: you speak English better than most native speakers, that's what all Germans say tho, weird
logi6000: no English is a fucked up language based off of Latin a language made by absolute dimwits
bravech: it's a carryover from the eternal wwii shame
mutrx: @bankzed @mrigor 0*100 = 0*200 = 0
michaelmaier007: i wrote "thinkink" instead of "thinking" lol
logi6000: I got to go to bed soon how much longer or should I go to bed
FaustPetrovich: @bankzed but coding in nano makes you 1000x times faster programmer dude
bravech: sleep is important don't stay up watching george program instead of sleeping
mutrx: notepad is how you get into the 9999x
mrigor: vim ai codes for you
FaustPetrovich: paper and pen oh don't even let me start it
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI
krouzux: !uptime
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI watch before AOC
bankzed: with that same logic, coding in ed will make you 10000000x faster
mutrx: @bankzed ed?
logi6000: I got to go to sleep its been fun. stay in school and don't take opioids.
mutrx: @logi6000 wise words
bankzed: 'man ed'
raidersans: good morning from the EU and happy upcoming holidays
mutrx: mutrx subscribed at Tier 1.
michaelmaier007: its not even the 16th of december there yet.
michaelmaier007: we live in the future xD
FaustPetrovich: coding in your imagination makes you → ∞
FaustPetrovich: faster
FaustPetrovich: at programming guys
btastical: yea its monday morning in germany rn
mrigor: @georgehotz would a prebuilt docker of tf version make this easier?
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI watch before AOC
mutrx: u missed my sub :(
BiTvon: @btastical Isn’t it still night basically
bravech: man I would hate for it to be monday
bravech: adderal = practice ?
btastical: @BiTvon some people are already up and working, early morning is more fitting, yes
michaelmaier007: @bravech youre not far away xD
alonkaliber: Do we love Elon Musk ?
BiTvon: Man people up and working at 5:45 am
bravech: do _you_ love elon musk?
FaustPetrovich: @mutrx at 2:10 -> hhkb with mx green wtf this video is cursed
peter35_: i like his rockets :)
ProfessorMagikarp0: this channel needs a KappaPride Elon Musk emote or a weed smoking Elon emote for subs LUL
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI watch before AOC
peter35_: launch today btw
mutrx: im a sub now
bravech: lmao sub request
alonkaliber: George did u eat pasta today..
bankzed: Da faq did i just watch? It was more psycho than the movie scene they were parodying
btastical: @BiTvon i'll leave at 6:30 aswell, but I couldn't sleep, so starting early = going home early
bravech: I've gotta think about that for a bit
mutrx: @FaustPetrovich yeah a bit cursed
raidersans: wait, subs get a free request ?
FaustPetrovich: my sub request is "make me immortal"
FaustPetrovich: "pls"
Vjasal: baiting for subs and donation smh
mutrx: my sub request is to have big p
BiTvon: @btastical Yeah I hear ya, I’m an insomniac European too
mrigor: https://hub.docker.com/r/tensorflow/tensorflow/tags?page=1&name=2. has 2 with gpu
bankzed: I wanna use my sub request to deny his sub request, that video was soul crushing
mutrx: my sub request is to have big pp
alonkaliber: @georgehotz maybe run a docker with TF installed alreday
braininavatt: Kappa
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI watch before AOC
peter35_: LUL
mutrx: :(
BiTvon: Stop
bravech: sub request: is there a future in software defined radio and should I get into it (have an opportunity)
bravech: @georgehotz
mutrx: my sub request what keyboard is that LUL
bankzed: try shift p it will give you P
Vjasal: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z-zxaKQfW6s @mutrx watch
peter35_: you have big p in another branch of the multiverse buddy
mutrx: @Vjasal baited
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI watch before AOC
tsAllySparkles: so the ai models run off android?
BiTvon: Big pp
mutrx: only rick and morty fans can understand
bravech: 15 mins to AOC
Vjasal: pp max
mutrx: is there an infographic to get big pp :(
braininavatt: pp up
michaelmaier007: currently eating pringles at 05:44 AM... fml
bankzed: they guys in that vid look like the worst people in South Park, SoMA
mrigor: @bravech where
btastical: so whats worse, handling multiple libraries, versions, and compiling or node_modules LUL
raidersans: it's really good
bankzed: s/they/the
BiTvon: Feelsbad when you can’t fix small pp with big pp
bankzed: I've had food at saison, it was meh
ProfessorMagikarp0: big pp is a state of mind nickiG
mrigor: chrome PIP extension is awesome https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/picture-in-picture-extens/hkgfoiooedgoejojocmhlaklaeopbecg?hl=en
BiTvon: @professormagikarp0 🤔
bankzed: Programming is only done in silicon valley Kappa
FaustPetrovich: @georgehotz can I make sub request?
tsAllySparkles: how did they kill defcon?
BiTvon: Isn’t internet produced and run in Silicon Valley
esence: SHOW US YOUR KEYBOARD!!!!!!!!!!!!!
btastical: what do you mean they killed defcon?
bravech: by attending it
mutrx: not even watching the vid :(
simmy7: @mrigor thank you for that, that's amazing
Jeppelelle: how did they kill defcon?
Vjasal: so anyway, what keyboards d oyou guys use
tsAllySparkles: i went to defcon.. did i kill it?
bankzed: obviously, @georgehotz Kappa = sarcasm
knilecrack: looks like it
BiTvon: He’s watching bro didn’t you hear him react earlier Kappa
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz did you always code in terminal or were you an ide person at some point? when/why did you switch?
mrigor: IDE is for plebs
ProfessorMagikarp0: its funny but not worth spamming the link 50 times LUL
mutrx: @BiTvon wot
PapaDukie: what is aoc
bankzed: why do they all look like product managers
jax05_: I remember being a n00b asking about keyboards and what ide to use LUL
FaustPetrovich: @georgehotz can I make sub request?
esence: Any success on running CARLA on macOS?
bravech: can we ban ide and keyboard talk
BiTvon: A good keyboard makes good code right?
bankzed: pardon my ignorance but what's AOC?
BiTvon: I want to make this app so
btastical: advent of code
bankzed: besides Alexandria ocasio-cortez
jax05_: I just realized you're talking about advent of code
peter35_: sorry ocasia cortez, the only AOC in my heart is #adventocode
mrigor: @esence hes ssh'd into a linux box
michaelmaier007: "dedotated wam"
Beraton: !uptime
zEveery: Sometimes it's showing TITAN X and some times Titan V. idk if means something
BiTvon: That poor kid doesn’t deserve that stuff
bankzed: Gentrifying AOC, I see Kappa
MrRobotVPN: just stumbled onto a archive video he did a live stream on youtube and saw his twitch link. Dude getohot is my idol. This is so cool I ant to get my CompTIA plus up here in canada and then go to college to get my C.I.T later.
mutrx: MrRobotVPN xd
BiTvon: Way you have a titan v?
bankzed: but he dropped out of college, lol
mrigor: @MrRobotVPN this stream is ai generated
esence: I love MrRobot. :>
MrRobotVPN: ai generated xD
bravech: the only big p is on PPP
MrRobotVPN: was just learning node-modules this month so this is really cool. was doing discord.js
mutrx: how old r u @MrRobotVPN
ProfessorMagikarp0: Kreygasm
esence: if you haven't dropped out, you will never make it
BiTvon: Dropped out of college but living in a 6K a month apartment
MrRobotVPN: in my 20's
BiTvon: Hey I’m in my 20s too
BiTvon: High five
mutrx: orange man won't get impeached
bankzed: wow, that's some fat pipes. In SD? or SF?
esence: orange man will happen the 2nd time
esence: you heard it here first
BiTvon: You’re telling me we can’t talk about keyboards but orange man and AOC is a ok
MrRobotVPN: yeah its a great show. wonder if geohot enjoys it Ramei Malek and Christan Slater are awesome.
bravech: invest now orange man pumping markets to get reelected
abstracticism: So what's going on here?
esence: @georgehotz , thoughts on Mr. Robot?
mutrx: advent of code
BiTvon: orange man will keep the stable but only cuz the field is weaker than my fathers knees
ProfessorMagikarp0: 9tails weeb rap needed Kreygasm
abstracticism: Yeah but what is he actually doing. Also lol this song
esence: try it, it's pretty good
bravech: mr robot season 1 was good the others were shit
michaelmaier007: try linkin park you will love it!!!!!!!
esence: cheesy, but good
BiTvon: Weebs out DansGame
moonify: You should try Mr Robot 9.5/10
mrigor: @georgehotz did you see PIP extension?
MrRobotVPN: yeah season 1 was the best first episode my favorite
BiTvon: Pp extension
vloood: these streams are great, i work at the same time and get shit done
bravech: ^^
esence: chat, let's bless geo, we gotta take 1st place in the competition!
bankzed: Moved out of bay area cuz of $6k apt. Now I pay $600 in Shenzhen
MrRobotVPN: geohots rap was the shit he needs to do another one.
BiTvon: @bankzed Damn
mrigor: @bankzed remote jobs pay less
bravech: that's a big move
giacpolish: George have you ever thought to stop with programming?
directrix13: Are you setting up Carla for automated testing of OpenPilot?
BiTvon: @bankzed Does the government check in on your morals
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg yikes @georgehotz
BiTvon: Imagine streaming your speakers through your mic
esence: raw stream
zEveery: https://github.com/migueldeicaza/TensorFlowSharp/issues/54 @georgehotz
hofergabriel: Why do number jokes not work in Octal? Because 7 10 11!
BiTvon: Raw shit dawg
michaelmaier007: https://youtu.be/kXYiU_JCYtU
bankzed: As far as Mr. Robot, boycotted it cuz the snitch from lulzsec works for the show
krouzux: can george get top 5 tonight?
esence: good luck!
braininavatt: glhf
AlexEDM: yowza
esence: 10!!!!!!!!!!!!
BiTvon: @bankzed Context?
raidersans: HYPE
risky_banana: actually hyped
moonify: you got it
esence: 5!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
J3rwin: lol
mutrx: oooooooooooooooo
esence: GO
sirleeroyjenkins: he def just snorted some coke
BiTvon: I saw the snort
abstracticism: he snorted code happiness
raidersans: 10 push ups when
abstracticism: do 20 pushups every 30m @georgehotz
BiTvon: If he wins he can self congratulate with more coke
MrRobotVPN: I love linux. Kali Liniux just had a new update
michaelmaier007: @sirleeroyjenkins coca cola you mean right?. shhhhh
BiTvon: Kappa HahaShrugRight
berghyfps: Hi all
mutrx: @MrRobotVPN do u program at all?
BiTvon: Hi bergy
mutrx: hi
michaelmaier007: f... need to prepare for school now. it was fun while it lasted.
BiTvon: Don’t you guys have pHoNeS?
death_gadget: Sounds like matrix/vector multiplication
MrRobotVPN: yeah did some C made a highscores database lookup when I was 13 for a MMORPG and tried acitonscript 2.0 to make a game because I was dumb. so now Ive been learning C# touched on java a bit and screwing with python
BiTvon: Acitone script sounds appropriate
J3rwin: how tf did someone already complete this
BiTvon: Come on George u got this
MrRobotVPN: yeah Im lost to. if anyone can do its george.
ummyeah1929: man i wish i could use vim like this
grey_street: Pog
borang: *clap*
alonkaliber: he = genuis LUL
ziggyzergling: PogChamp
braininavatt: SeemsGood
michaelmaier007: ANELE
berghyfps: @ummyeah1929 Me too. I'm a vim noob, tryna learn it so I can be like george one day
BiTvon: The fuck
alonkaliber: There are crazy good programmers in this world huh.. to think 30 people had already finished it before him
jax05_: @alonkaliber right?? lol
ummyeah1929: @berghyfps usually just use nano but seeing someone quick with vim is really impressive and looks like itd save lots of time
mutrx: should have written it in go
btastical: the first problem was not too hard if you think about it
MrRobotVPN: my internet is shit hope I can watch this later in clips or someone archives it.
alonkaliber: @jax05_ for real
michaelmaier007: @mrrobotvpn he posts his streams on yt later.
alonkaliber: Now were optimizing the program..
adibaby04: the hell happened
adibaby04: last i checked we were doing openpilot
ummyeah1929: meme o ize Pog
michaelmaier007: goodbye guys school time :(
mutrx: ew memoization
KNOOKEL_HEAD: meme o ize
ummyeah1929: meme o ize just for efficiency?
abhb09: What is carla?
jax05_: @MrRobotVPN did you lower resolution?
jax05_: @adibaby04 he's doing advent of code
Waywoah: What's the goal of this problem?
mag_m3m0ry: it's Monday morning. should I go to work or watch this?
MrMcaustin1: ALways watch george
mag_m3m0ry: facts
jax05_: @mag_m3m0ry watch geo :)
mutrx: what are the first 8 digits
MrMcaustin1: numpy matrix?
jax05_: monkaS
mutrx: @mods
death_gadget: 🔨
jax05_: the mods can't hear you now :)
mutrx: AOC
MrMcaustin1: All the timeouts
MrMcaustin1: Ha
MrMcaustin1: Was setting up tmux
krouzux: gottem
lemonboxed: when im ded bury me in fractions
MrMcaustin1: You should know better
ProfessorMagikarp0: who just Thanos'd the chat LUL
jax05_: ok thanos LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: i dont feel so good mods
ProfessorMagikarp0: *turns to dust*
MrMcaustin1: 4 timeouts
MrMcaustin1: oof
Emmaralds: what is advent of code?
MrMcaustin1: They can talk in 10 minutes
mutrx: google
PiroFloydian: can he not use numpy
MrMcaustin1: Emmaralds its a coding competition of sorts
death_gadget: 🔨 🔨 🔨 🔨 🔨
MrMcaustin1: He can, hes just laazy PiroFloydian
RishabhDeepSingh: pajaHey_HF pajaHey_HF pajaHey_HF
PiroFloydian: oh lol
J3rwin: doesn't tourist compete in these
MrMcaustin1: Lowkey miss my mac, do I dual boot linux?
jax05_: go for it MrMcaustin1
Eastonn: what mouse is he using Kappa
attiluh: Kappa
MrMcaustin1: Eastonn you sneaky bastard
Eastonn: got eem
TeaLeafi: the great Geo <3
Eastonn: if i ask noob questions is that bannable or is that ok
MrMcaustin1: You can ask
Eastonn: what language is this?
attiluh: Python
zEveery: python
Eastonn: NotLikeThis
paulfreeman: english
jax05_: PogChamp
MrMcaustin1: mutrx really?
braininavatt: Clap
braininavatt: LUL
PiroFloydian: what (if any) is learning curve like switching from using ides to terminal/vi/etc?
death_gadget: LUL
attiluh: Pepega @mutrx
ProfessorMagikarp0: nickiGun
ProfessorMagikarp0: mutrx spam
maverick_twitch_: so fast
attiluh: @pirofloydian Use Nano
attiluh: :)
death_gadget: @PiroFloydian Are you talking about auto-complete? There isn't that much learning curve IMO.
Eastonn: LUL
braininavatt: F
mutrx: wow ok
Eastonn: LUL LUL LUL
braininavatt: hahahaaa
MrMcaustin1: Alright mutrx you done
mutrx: :(
braininavatt: you had one chance
zEveery: gcd only returns positive int.
ProfessorMagikarp0: HahaCat
ethancruize: when CTF/hacking again?
mutrx: i think memoization was the way to go
mutrx: i lost Kreygasm
postalrat: memeization?
mutrx: if you memoize the first signal, and then the repeats can be computed O(1)
MrMcaustin1: memorization or caching?
Eastonn: is he solving a problem right now from a website or something?
J3rwin: advent of code
MrMcaustin1: https://adventofcode.com
SilvanoGJr: looks like adventofcode . com
mutrx: if you memoize the first signal, and then the repeats can be computed O(1)
TinksFn: hey
MrMcaustin1: Yeah mutrx he should do that
TinksFn: i need help with my javascript bug
MrMcaustin1: But I think hes in his own world rn
TinksFn: can anyone help me
mutrx: yeah he's too focused to read chat @mrigor
PiroFloydian: @death_gadget basically i dont do much in the terminal and mostly use ides and was wondering what the switching process was like/why people do/dont do it
mutrx: @MrMcaustin1
GCOutwitt: GCOutwitt subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! Appreciate everything you've done since the first iPhone back in the day
TinksFn: help
MrMcaustin1: GCOutwitt welcome!
JohnEGQ: JohnEGQ subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
MrMcaustin1: JohnEGQ welcome back!
mutrx: @PiroFloydian its really just a personal preference, doesn't make u any better. people do it for less "distractions"
mutrx: and its a steep learning curve
iammimilolo: What is your IQ?
Eastonn: big brain 5Head
bankzed: This looks like a problem to solve with convolution, maybe the FFT is a hint
mutrx: at least 5
alonkaliber: George = LUL
devicerailway845: "Science & Technology" is a more active category than "basic programming" for this
ProfessorMagikarp0: u dont want "Science & Technology" normies tho DansGame
mutrx: @ProfessorMagikarp0 gets it
Eastonn: TRUE DansGame
mufeedvh: yeah
red123123: Hi HumbleLife
bankzed: You were in the right direction with matrix math, I made a matrix of the input and the pattern and doing multiplication of the two
alonkaliber: @bankzed did you solve the problem..?
red123123: !time
mufeedvh: i have math exam tomorrow
ImJ4Gu4R: How many hour now?
TDxSK8: he's been love for 4 hours
TDxSK8: *live
ImJ4Gu4R: Alright @TDxSK8 Thanks.
bankzed: I used i^n to generate the shifting pattern
bankzed: i being sqrt(-1)
bankzed: Well and 1
mufeedvh: what is he trying to solve with this script? @bankzed
bankzed: https://adventofcode.com/2019/day/16
MrMcaustin1: Advent of Code day 15 pt. 2 mufeedvh
mascer95: @mufeedvh I guess the newest coding challenge on advent of code
bravech: Lolf
TDxSK8: was about to say lol
ProfessorMagikarp0: how do people know to ask that first like 99% of the time LUL
mufeedvh: Thank You, got it
mascer95: @parogen it’s a forbidden question. Can’t find the rules though
TDxSK8: yes
adibaby04: @georgehotz for cereal, when a new message is being made, is it by default a CarEvent? Im trying to add documentation
mascer95: @parogen ohh yeah says in the info box do not ask about keyboard
MrMcaustin1: mascer95 dont mention the k word ;)
adibaby04: yo @georgehotz kinda important
mascer95: @mrmcaustin1 alright
bravech: Or talk about drugs
bravech: F
mutrx: memoization
mascer95: @bravech yesterday George was talking about it pretty openly
ThePotatoProgrammer: Time to just start over
mutrx: time to sudo rm -rf *
ProfessorMagikarp0: need to train under a waterfall for clarity nickiG
mascer95: @mrmcaustin1 how often do you stream?
MrMcaustin1: Me? Not that much
mascer95: @mrmcaustin1 alright, was just curious!
MrMcaustin1: no worries
bankzed: Yeah, it's like convolution of the input with the output, eventually it will converge (all zeros)
ONEabdo: Hi georgehotz
ONEabdo: how you doing ?
Waywoah: Has anyone else solved it yet?
zEveery: 78 peoples
mascer95: Are there any tips on doing AoC? I only started coding a month ago and did a Codecademy Course which I feel like only helped understanding the basics. Do I work with Stackoverflow and just google? Or better follow tutorials?
bankzed: yeah, made mine 2x faster by not doing the math on the zeros inputs and zero phase patterns
MrMcaustin1: mascer95 you will never know everything with programming its an always evolving thing
MrMcaustin1: Just do stuff
MrMcaustin1: Do the codes
mascer95: @mrmcaustin1 first day was pretty good! had to figure out how to work with an ide, because codecademy has an online interpreter. Second day is tough already :)
bankzed: you can do element wise multiplication and addition, that's what I did
MrMcaustin1: Haha mascer95 I remember when I was that way. Just sit down and anytime you are confused just google it
bankzed: https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/matrix-manipulation-python/
MrMcaustin1: bankzed hes not really looking at chat
mascer95: I was about to say the same! He doesn’t want help he said :D
mascer95: @mrmcaustin1 yeah Google is really helpful in that sense! Thanks for the advice!
MrMcaustin1: Of course
alonkaliber: How many people finished the challenge already ?
zEveery: use CUDA to run it, profit
MrMcaustin1: If you have any questions just DM me
bankzed: He said he gave up, lol.
zEveery: Kappa
alonkaliber: @bankzed did u finish the challenge...?
mascer95: @alonkaliber I believe someone said 78 before
alonkaliber: @mascer95 i see
imfunniee: *thonk intensifies*
bankzed: I haven't submitted it yet, I'm doing optimizations
mutrx: LUL
TheArc_TV: what is carla?
adibaby04: use a fourier transform to multiply LUL
tsAllySparkles: i got a 2019 kia forte... and i bought a devkit.. hopefully it'll integrate well fingers crossed
MrMcaustin1: George dont forget to change the stream name
MrMcaustin1: *title
tsAllySparkles: but if not i'll make it work :D
archeadis: use numpy and pypy
mutrx: why aren't u memoizing
mrmusicmaine: Just popped back in. This ain’t Carla tho, I can’t see the url.. what’s the challenge?
imfunniee: advent
alonkaliber: I think it is a matrix..
ImJ4Gu4R: Yea, carla is done?
adibaby04: wait just do it in C the performance should improve a bit?
mascer95: @mrmusicmaine Advent of Code 2019 Day 16
mutrx: @adibaby04 LUL
adibaby04: i mean complexity rn is O(n^2) but it could be a faster O(n^2)
mutrx: @johnnyhammastix @adibaby04 or @georgehotz
MrMcaustin1: Which guy johnnyhammastix
mrmusicmaine: Fire
P0LY: monkaS
adibaby04: wym i cant code
adibaby04: ah
MrMcaustin1: johnnyhammastix lets be nice
alonkaliber: @johnnyhammastix be nice cmonBruh
MrMcaustin1: and goodbye
alonkaliber: LUL
mutrx: someone's having a bad day
imfunniee: *life
P0LY: evo19MindBlown artoSmooth
mutrx: he said you couldn't code
mutrx: LUL
alonkaliber: He said you coded bad..
MrMcaustin1: He said that a gorilla can code better than you
veomx: he ask about your keyboard
ONEabdo: Xd
ThePotatoProgrammer: lol
ImJ4Gu4R: PogChamp
polysoulz: hey hey BCWarrior
zup_zup: what leaderboard?
zup_zup: oh advent
mutrx: he gave up LUL
ThePotatoProgrammer: there is a stripe of diagonal ones in the printout
mutrx: not the zeros
red_plex: hey just joining, what are you trying to do with Carla ? RL ?
ThePotatoProgrammer: linear algebra upper triangle rule looks like
TheArc_TV: Convolution Theorem :puke:
TheArc_TV: My professor hit the whole class with a Convolution Theorem from a challenge project on one of our exams
alonkaliber: @georgehotz do you love mathematics?
C4TFive: Why is the light from your screen so yellow? are you using F.Lux?
MrMcaustin1: C4TFive yeah he is using flux
MrSnoopDog: this is pretty cool
PiroFloydian: why not abs and mod
lemonboxed: is this day 16
MrMcaustin1: yes
alonkaliber: This is actually really hard huh...
zEveery: As I'm looking u can use FFT (Fast Fourier Transform).
adibaby04: use the strassen algorithm right?
hoopchamp: get all of the eigenvalues. wont help, but at least you'll have the eigenvalues
VanityShowcase: I like your github profile picture
adibaby04: who?
鼻史: list comprehension PogChamp
TheArc_TV: Pog
zup_zup: oh cool i didn't know you founded comma.ai
ThePotatoProgrammer: What happens if you invert the matrix?
adibaby04: why would you invert it?
ThePotatoProgrammer: Just to see what happens :)
alonkaliber: is this largeee machine his working on, is vagrant box ?
kkkizune: he dead?
mufeedvh: whats on the floor?
ThePotatoProgrammer: That is the armrest lol
BWalks530: are you computing every value in the matrix or just the top triangle?
nikhilr14: !uptime
ThePotatoProgrammer: LOOOOOL
mufeedvh: lol
ThePotatoProgrammer: monkaS
MrMcaustin1: gottem
nikhilr14: lets go he's streaming
ViktorTV: @georgehotz what is the goal? also this looks like upper triangular matrix so maybe it's something with that
adibaby04: fill us in maybe we can help
georgehotz: https://adventofcode.com/2019/day/16
bankzed: Machine learning?
adibaby04: what??
alonkaliber: @georgehotz the guys who solved this are most mathematicians aswell i assume
adibaby04: how is this machine learning?
FoxMcWeezer: How good are your probability and stats skills @georgehotz
MrMcaustin1: Look at the subrededit
MrMcaustin1: https://www.reddit.com/r/adventofcode/
C4TFive: Isnt this Basic Programming? Kappa
nikhilr14: isnt he doing carla ?
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz the output back half is just the reverse partial sums of the input back half.
adibaby04: Because the input string is repeated 10000 times, and the pattern also repeats, can't you just compute the answer for a portion of the input string, and then use multiplication to remove the bulk of the work?
MrMcaustin1: For part 2, someone used partial sums to compute contiguous sums, and then multiplied those sums by 0, 1 or -1 accordingly. For the first position, you have to compute N sums, then N/2, then N/3 and so on. So overall complexity should be N * (1 1/2 ...) = N * log(N), since the harmonic series converges to logarithm.
bankzed: used SciPi to convert to sparse matrix, by chopping out all the zeroes
bankzed: *SciPy
lemonboxed: like a factorization of some sort
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz partial sums
MrMcaustin1: And its a Unitriangular matrix
Eorphor: doesnt it look like time shifted oscillating sequence? Maybe there is a clever way to build it
ViktorTV: @mrmcaustin1 I told him that alrey
MrMcaustin1: Yeah hes hyper focused
nikhilr14: https://www.reddit.com/r/adventofcode/comments/ebai4g/2019_day_16_solutions/
adibaby04: the latter half condition
qlutoo: I just joined but is this not just computing A^n * x where A is a matrix and x is a vector. With n large you can do repeated squaring to quickly calculate A^n in O(log n)
qlutoo: Ah nvm
lemonboxed: theres a reason why 90% of mathematicians have wacky hairstyles
Stevein: toes? yuck
ViktorTV: @georgehotz LOOK UP MATRIX DIAGONALIZATION
adibaby04: @georgehotz the latter half condition makes it more effecient
alonkaliber: @georgehotz think cutting the matrix
alonkaliber: if you want @georgehotz https://www.reddit.com/r/adventofcode/comments/ebai4g/2019_day_16_solutions/
BiTvon: This puzzle kind of owned you
Particle_x: duhleeNani duhleeNani
BiTvon: Keep in mind I have no idea how do it either but still
MrMcaustin1: Just look up the solutions
Stevein: dream of a solution
CaptCalifornia: holy fuck ur still working
Eorphor: Ok what I think but it’s probably wrong. If you know the size of the final matrix, you know the sequence is designated to the needed line. At the end do you need to compute the whole matrix. Line gives you the « repeating pattern » if line 3 its 2 zeros, then 3 ones, 3 zeros, 3 minus ones etc.. IDK if it’s possible ..
lemmywemmy: the only thing that sticks out to me is that the matrix isn't green
alonkaliber: @georgehotz let me tell you this, part2 can run in 2 seconds..
ViktorTV: @georgehotz YES LETS DREAM OF THE CODE. LIKE THAT ONE MAGE SMART KID THAT DREAMS IN CODE. Kappa
adibaby04: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DBXZWB_dNsw&t=273s
adibaby04: ^^^
adibaby04: dream in code
alonkaliber: Many interesting solutions
ViktorTV: yup @adibaby04 such a fucking fake video lmao
BiTvon: I think it’s a reference to the pop culture version of matrix movies and all
adibaby04: IKR
alonkaliber: @georgehotz The key observation for part 2 is that if your sequence has length n and you want to compute the value of the next phase at index i with i > n/2, then it's just the sum of all of the elements with index at least i. Therefore, we only need to compute the sequence for indices higher than the given offset at every phase, and we can do so in linear time.
adibaby04: YES
adibaby04: NO SHIT GEORGE
zEveery: This is an upper unitriangular, and all triangular part is one (upper side) cuz we never reach the 3st 0 from pattern base. I think if u just use the submatrix adding from the N term till the end, u get the new term.
Abnico: hi
alonkaliber: @georgehotz you had that...
MrMcaustin1: Its okay george you are still smarter than us
vay_man: hi from India...
ViktorTV: go back to India
ViktorTV: xqcEZ xqcEZ xqcEZ xqcEZ
indaylancer: SoBayed
lemonboxed: scam puzzle
lemonboxed: doink
zup_zup: do you just use default vim?
adibaby04: no dude
adibaby04: its clearly not
TheArc_TV: does anyone know a good resource to improve using linux, ubuntu specifically
TheArc_TV: my workstation at school is linux and i feel like a snail
ViktorTV: I have a resource @thearc_tv
TheArc_TV: Kappa incoming
TheArc_TV: i dont trust u
ViktorTV: I mean it is kinda a Kappa but I was going to be an asshole and say using it is a good resource
ViktorTV: buy there is truth in that
braininavatt: Jebaited
P0LY: LUL
lemmywemmy: maxwel11KKona
MrMcaustin1: hahaha
tsAllySparkles: question- these LKAS systems are all pretty standardized between car brands??
tsAllySparkles: who makes them?
indaylancer: SoBayed
vay_man: @TheArc_TV linux is the best resourse for linux..
lemonboxed: real puzzles are hard to make
alonkaliber: @georgehotz they wanted to make people tyhink extra extra hard, but in reallity solution was way easier i guess.
lemonboxed: easier to scam
RishabhDeepSingh: pajaHandsUp_SG pajaHandsUp_SG pajaHandsUp_SG
BiTvon: 😆
Particle_x: elite5Gachi
vay_man: whats going on?
WoockieCookiee: Hello from Spain George, 7 am here
red123123: !uptime
zEveery: https://www.reddit.com/r/adventofcode/comments/ebai4g/2019_day_16_solutions/fb3ksil/ linear time
ViktorTV: @georgehotz how to get job at Google?
vay_man: solve such probs better than others
lemonboxed: cumsum ?
BiTvon: Lmao
vay_man: lul
ViktorTV: @vay_man that was an obvious joke but do you seriously think this is at all relevant to actual coding?
vay_man: what do you think actual coding is?
sanaki13: ofc it isnt, but thats how you get a job at Google lmao
ViktorTV: how will this help me get a job at Google? do they offer it to winners or something
sanaki13: they ask algorithmic puzzle questions in their job interviews, like almost everywhere else
vay_man: google don't need coders they need problem solvers
BiTvon: Google is evil anyway
ArcherCreatlol: ^ Truee
ViktorTV: yes, general algorithmic questions, not some specific shit like this
MrMcaustin1: Normally for programming interviews they focus on the way which you solve the problem and then your coding skills
vay_man: yes
vay_man: they just want you to solve everything in linear time
vay_man: or less
MrMcaustin1: Not always
lemonboxed: google doesn't really need anything
lemonboxed: they already have it all
lua_320: Google is a piece of shit
borang: classmate just got hired
alonkaliber: They're at a point this just fuck B1tchs
vay_man: google is dope
vay_man: wahts he solving anyways. I came late
MrMcaustin1: Advent of Code
vay_man: ?
MrMcaustin1: https://adventofcode.com/2019/about vay_man
vay_man: got it bro
MrMcaustin1: Do you have any type of caching implemented?
iamreclusive: @georgehotz Thank you very much, 'geohotz'; from an old-school user of a Jail-Broken iPhone 1 (1.1.1). :)
MrMcaustin1: Or would any work in this case?
BiTvon: Woah woah that’s illegal tutorials
JonThomasK: your not hired
BiTvon: Thank you for coming in
vay_man: nope...this is purely how you reduce time complexity
bankzed: O( n log n)
vay_man: its brilliant
vay_man: I mean anyone can do it using brute force,, but thats not the point
BiTvon: If you wanna win brute force is cool though 😎
bankzed: You can do a conv of the signal and the pattern (DFT) but also have to take into consideration of the special cases
Knarez: the harmonic series diverges Kappa
vay_man: @bankzed those were my initial thoughts
mikey9988: mutrx in the dms LUL
mufeedvh: cool stuff
BiTvon: Lmao
BiTvon: Good work George
MrMcaustin1: GG
vay_man: Ik
ziggyzergling: being not a noob
ArcherCreatlol: PogChamp
zEveery: GG, take a drink to celebrate
jay_al97: did you get Carla to work
BiTvon: Can you read mutrx message on stream
mufeedvh: da best
vay_man: thats easy for you to say
BiTvon: Before you go
mikey9988: Ahead of Curve EZ Clap
bankzed: It was a BS problem due to the special case
vay_man: number 1
BiTvon: Nothing disregard, disawow
zEveery: wow I can see some WoW player here
mikey9988: LUL
MrMcaustin1: cmu = Carnegie Mellon University
MrMcaustin1: ?
bankzed: Any RIT?
bankzed: lol
toolegit2quit_: Is CMU worth it ?
MrMcaustin1: Ha almost applied to go there
mikey9988: are melons tasty?
peter35_: any cornelll?
MrMcaustin1: Dont have the grades tho and dont care
MrMcaustin1: You can click there name to see who they are
zEveery: You have an strong math base or just the basics? Also u find it really important for commercial development
zEveery: ? *
Knarez: what did you leave for
jay_al97: why did you leave
Knarez: LUL CLASSIC
lemonboxed: grills
bankzed: Haha, I use to sit in CMU classes while I was at RIT when I was at a Co-op in Pittsburgh, why I dropped out of RIT
vay_man: to work for google
toolegit2quit_: Scholarship?
Eastonn: HotPokket U BETTER NOT
Eastonn: Kappa
lemonboxed: so second time was also grills
lemonboxed: in politics
BiTvon: Leaving for a girl uh oh
MrMcaustin1: Update your wikipedia to update why you left
KNOOKEL_HEAD: i dropped out of elementary and now im a billionaire
mikey9988: didn't allow him to liberally use the N word cmonBruh
montecarlo: three semesters??
BiTvon: Politics ruining another young mans dream
zackartz: zackartz subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Eastonn: doctrine
KNOOKEL_HEAD: just hackthebox 4Head
montecarlo: 5Head
BiTvon: Ahh yes
montecarlo: e.g. ?
vay_man: dogma.
Eastonn: not doctrine but a certain type of thinking only?
jay_al97: SA college
BiTvon: The communist dogma Kappa
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
montecarlo: KEKW
bankzed: RIT has jumped the shark for sure
mikey9988: PepeHands
lemonboxed: too many students playing the game in uni
zEveery: It almost like feel. I do CS, I really like the math things and everything I'm learning about complexity, compilers... But sometimes I feel like it's pushing me away from market. There's a lot of old techs on university.
MrMcaustin1: I am currently in college on the west coast and theres so many reasons to hate it and love it
vay_man: did you create a site to rate hotness of girls ?
picklesareok: i could learn everything i have learned in school from better resources for free
picklesareok: im paying for social credit
BiTvon: @vay_man lmao
Eastonn: @vay_man LUL GOOD ONE
MrMcaustin1: But I am at a very research based college
BiTvon: That’s fucking hilarious
brevan04: Good morning Geo. 1:30 in Omaha
red123123: perfect
KNOOKEL_HEAD: 8:30AM in eu
Anionz: ps5 coming out soon geohot, time to dust off the old lawsuit?
tornpaperyoyos: !uptime
vay_man: 1 pm in India
BiTvon: College tried to Box him out of jail breaking :/
zEveery: Anionz question hahahah
vay_man: me
mufeedvh: me
montecarlo: me :)
KNOOKEL_HEAD: people that arent n00bs
red123123: 10.30 am turkey hi
vay_man: I think I found
BiTvon: Me also
Hunted9000: o/
mutrx: im back
vay_man: the truth
tornpaperyoyos: how long has george been streaming?
mutrx: oh did he solve part 2/
montecarlo: yes i found it
MrMcaustin1: The quest for the truth is hard but it gets side tracked by like whats the point of snails
Waywoah: What do you mean by truth?
vay_man: its disturbing
mutrx: hahah how painfully
lemonboxed: truth seekers are always noobs
TinksFn: hey
TinksFn: what were you coding
mutrx: what did you end up doing
red123123: which days do you open
montecarlo: advent of code
lemonboxed: scam problems teach you alot about life
BiTvon: Life is a scam
BiTvon: So the puzzles follow suit
TinksFn: what os advent of code
mutrx: love these end of stream rants
montecarlo: @TinksFn https://adventofcode.com/2019/
Knarez: what would you say happened to it
TinksFn: i dont underestand the website
vay_man: what happennthen?
montecarlo: daily coding puzzles thats all
TinksFn: ohhh
tornpaperyoyos: @georgehotz show us some of your advent of code solutions plz
brevan04: Google founders are gone now, for the better?
montecarlo: implicit association? whats the purpose?
Iliftmymousealot: Iliftmymousealot subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 9 months! that Google Businessmodel though, high Hacking brains
Eastonn: is it a so called bias test?
gary_burton: those tests are BS
bankzed: It's way worse here in Shenzhen, the scam is larger.
zEveery: Thanks for the HahaCat @iliftmymousealot
BiTvon: 🤔 🤔
Hunted9000: Cheer100
BiTvon: ... based?
Eastonn: @georgehotz there is so many factors not taken into consideration with those implicit bias tests
iv4nhoe: @georgehotz back on Twitch I see HeyGuys
TheCellarDoor: @georgehotz
mutrx: orange man bad
lemonboxed: if google isnt running google who is ?? dun dun dun
picklesareok: it feels impossible to escape
zEveery: I saw yesterday u master some languages.. How u master languages ? Doing puzzles and looking for documentation? Actually I kinda struggle to learn a new language (I mean, masterize it. Start knowing the tricks.)
gary_burton: it's important to a faction of managment, it's about power battles between factions
brisingr1031: ratirlRich ratirlRich ratirlRich
picklesareok: LUL
mutrx: someone needs to wipe the server
georgehotz: https://www.scottaaronson.com/blog/?p=3376
mikey9988: factions monkaS
MrMcaustin1: Lets talk about amazon now. How they have literally taken over everything
innocent_shkreli: the real problem with google is they have billions in cash sitting around yet they hardly innovate
vay_man: steve jobs has truely left silicon valley
mutrx: amen
gary_burton: @georgehotz I hope you used a number theoretic transform for day 16 part 2 and got the whole answer LUL
montecarlo: should i got back to grad school for math?
tornpaperyoyos: can you show us some of your AoC solutions?
lemonboxed: isnt amazon just a giant logistics company
MrMcaustin1: TinksFn monkaS
mutrx: @mods
KNOOKEL_HEAD: monkaS
montecarlo: monkaS
zEveery: cuz everyone gonna starts asking that. spamming like crazy
Eastonn: everyone asks about it thats why LUL
ArcherCreatlol: monkaS /
brisingr1031: @lemonboxed aws is p much becoming that
TalonFire: what mouse you got?
p4ri: why u so smat
mufeedvh: you've interned at SpaceX right?
Zanderly: LUL
MrMcaustin1: uh oh
montecarlo: BANNED
brickvo: you need bttv
MrMcaustin1: timeout incoming
mutrx: error unused symbol keyboard
picklesareok: too many rules
brisingr1031: @georgehotz what finger do you use to hit the spacebar?? /s
TheCellarDoor: @georgehotz if you add /chat at the end of your twitch url you can have a window with only your chat
gary_burton: need to keep the mechanical keyboard enthusiasts at bay LUL
montecarlo: gotta follow the rules
Knarez: why didnt thinks work out at spacex? Kappa
KNOOKEL_HEAD: bye @TinksFn
mikey9988: right thumb DansGame
ArmanTheCyber: geohot do a reaction test online
mutrx: you were an intern?
vay_man: who watched last season of silicon valley?
Knarez: screen vs tmux and why both
lemonboxed: uses pinky to hit space bar... mad man
montecarlo: LULW
bankzed: Did you reach your goal for IG?
Roundlay: PogChamp
mutrx: f
I_am_paranoid: but what mouse do you use? pretty sure it's some mouses boost programming skill
hardtarget4: got em
braininavatt: I just noticed I use my left thumb SeemsGood
red123123: lul
Particle_x: LMAO
mutrx: we all can't get banned if we band together brothers
braininavatt: ^^^
montecarlo: you got first mutrx
montecarlo: go*
KNOOKEL_HEAD: what is the brand of your fridge
mutrx: k-k-k-k-k-nvm
Eastonn: rebel against the system PogChamp
braininavatt: monkaS
tornpaperyoyos: you sure as hell can actually
anxova: OpieOP
jax05_: :O
ArcherCreatlol: monkaS
lemonboxed: fight the power
Particle_x: monkaS
Eastonn: dictator monkaS
archeadis: @georgehotz What mouse do you use?
MrMcaustin1: I can setup an automated script to ban anyone who mentions the k word
walsh9: thanos snap for bans
vay_man: lol
gary_burton: it's Hong Kong vs China monkaS
Knarez: what's the last video game you played
myuchelys: our powers combined..I'll start: W
Roundlay: what webcam do you use?
TalonFire: what's your favorite scale to play?
Eastonn: H
brickvo: do you watch twitch streamers ?
mufeedvh: i am hungry too
borang: 어떤 키보드
vay_man: c minor
Roundlay: You can in settings
mutrx: what if we're talking about the instrument keyboard
MrMcaustin1: I can set it as one
brevan04: Cinnamon Rolls & Chilli is a meal in NE
walsh9: you can set banwords in your settings somewhere
hardtarget4: there's a way to do it
archeadis: @georgehotz Was wondering what mouse you were using?
Hunted9000: do we get banned if ask to see the setup
picklesareok: the k word*
lemonboxed: the keyword
Knarez: room tour video when???!?
Eastonn: @georgehotz how about brands of you know what, can i talk about those
mikey9988: what skateboard do you have ? Kappa
montecarlo: follow george on isnta to find out more about his k word!
zEveery: I saw yesterday u master some languages.. How u master languages ? Doing puzzles and looking for documentation? Actually I kinda struggle to learn a new language (I mean, masterize it. Start knowing the tricks.)
MrMcaustin1: Can't use it now
braininavatt: what if I used to play the keyboard when I was 10 Kappa
georgehotz: you whats your keyboard
brisingr1031: k e y b o a r d ??
montecarlo: ur a mod
Knarez: what is your keyboard
montecarlo: you can say it
ZippyBot92: can you point your camera down so we can see your mouse
Knarez: Kappa
braininavatt: Jebaited
MrMcaustin1: scam
ArcherCreatlol: mine is stealseries ty for asking :)
montecarlo: we can't
ArmanTheCyber: k3yboard?
MrMcaustin1: twitch liedf
montecarlo: keeb
walsh9: LUL
ArcherCreatlol: LUL
p4ri: keybaord
I_am_paranoid: keyboard!
Knarez: keyboard
p4ri: keyboard
mikey9988: mod everyone :)
lemonboxed: keyboard
montecarlo: keyboard
mufeedvh: lol
mutrx: wekeyboard
ArcherCreatlol: keyboard
vay_man: keebod
montecarlo: LMAO
Eastonn: keyboard
I_am_paranoid: pls no ban
bankzed: this convo is worse than K Hole
KNOOKEL_HEAD: doesnt work OMEGALUL
Roundlay: Your message wasn't posted due to conflicts with the channel's moderation settings.
mutrx: REVOLT BROTHERs
MadArkadian: lmao
montecarlo: BAN US ALL LIKE YOU SAID
MrMcaustin1: Ha sub only
Iliftmymousealot: no
mutrx: subs only gang
brisingr1031: ripppp
zackartz: rip
mutrx: if we could have a whole stream like the end of s tream
Iliftmymousealot: 😬
braininavatt: braininavatt subscribed at Tier 1.
mutrx: :)
braininavatt: freeeee
MrMcaustin1: welcome braininavatt
Iliftmymousealot: 1m2019
FaustPetrovich: mod deleted my message, I'm a sub, wtf?
mutrx: sub gang
bankzed: about to gift everyone a sub if they promise not to say the K word
mutrx: are u gonna buy 1m2020.com?
MrMcaustin1: 1m2019.com is still down
FaustPetrovich: unsubscribe
mutrx: i'll trade u 1m2020 for $50
MrMcaustin1: No I just tested it
MrMcaustin1: It broke
mutrx: LUL web developer
MrMcaustin1: Wait it works now
MrMcaustin1: just slow af
Iliftmymousealot: See you
bankzed: Gotta thot it up for 1m subs
braininavatt: HahaDoge HahaDoge